Vox popular people's voice
How clever a little flickering box
Telling the sinners what they want to hear take the fight upstairs
Make hell great again. You're right. It's a wonderful idea
But you forgot who's in charge of the revolution
Attention you have it you brought up my wife
You brought up my chains. You thought you were so clever pulling at the pains
Your mouthy little bitch with your screams so bright
You just reminded
Sleeping God about his life
They thought they'd won this crown wings can read chains can be undone
And I'm the one past is over. Mr. Vox you've served your purpose
Gather the sinners, we're going upstairs.
Charlie, you'll understand.
This is the only way.
The original nightmare, coming out in the night air
Fall asleep when I'm right there
When your mind's eye, if you die there
Then you're mine, boy, I don't fight there
You think I'm terrified of right here?
27 years, you'll be asleepy
I'll be creeping up in your dreams
It's a long time, I am relentless
That's your bring your printers
Taking your appendix
Did you take this?
And that's it, please
And I'll help you
I get reckless
And death is infectious
Punch you when you're precious
I dare Pennywise, mad choice, hot you out in broad daylight
Show you nightmares, do you pay a white like me?
I don't need sleep, send you six feet deep, deep, clean,
sweet for your peaks when I see deep leaves
And I find anything you need and I'll use that
One fragment to your stagnant
And you can't move, it's a fragment of your mind
And anytime, got a small timeframe, many crimes happen
Then I'll disappear to the darkness, come and get it
This is a battle for your nightmares
Hide now with my sight players
Can you hide?
No
Can you run?
Know where you can go
Now with my sight players
Know where you can still
Just a copy
I'm the Mentec
Visionary and inventive
Like your worst fears coming in
Ha!
Clown head meet the blade
Handle kill children
Easy target
What a bill
Just a little clown with some makeup
My face is the real fear
Done this eight times and I'm still here
I'm legend
Get your way to
I'm the reason those kids stay up
Bravewood Raphacy
You raise a bad name
Conventional wisdom has it that the grail bloodline is sacred because it came from Christ,
a man still considered by much of the world to be the true Son of God.
And yet the dynasty of kings who descended from this bloodline were known as sorcerer
kings, some of whom hinted or even stated outright that they were in fact descendants
of Lucifer.
A number of authors claim this thesis is true, but they are predominantly hardcore Christian
and stop well short of explaining why they believe this, or of giving any tangible details to
substantiate their claims. Says one, in typical Gnostic fashion, descendants of the Morovinans
claim to have the blood of both Christ and Satan in their veins.
Given the fact that this theme, or a variation of it, recurs with some regularity, and given
that it would appear to be consistent with the sort of dual vibe which permeates the
saga of this bloodline, I began to wonder if there might not be some traditions from
which such a notion could have arisen.
At length, several were discovered.
Firstly, let's remember that this bloodline descended from a figure who equates with the biblical Cain.
In certain rabbinic law, we come across the very interesting notion that Cain was not the son of Adam, but of Samuel.
It was thought that when Samuel appeared to Eve as a serpent, he seduced her.
The fruit of that union was Cain.
Now Samuel was a fallen angel, essentially the Judaic Lucifer.
If the Morovinans knew of this version of the story, which they no doubt did, and believed
it, it could be the basis of their alleged assertion that they possessed the blood of
both Christ and Lucifer.
Equally Luciferian in its connotations says that he was the son of Adam's first wife,
Lilith. She had been the consort of God before coming to earth as a fallen angel. The full
details of her story are probably too well known to bear repeating here, but it's interesting
that of the two alternate traditions concerning Cain's parentage, both involve the Luciferian
that the lily is known to have taken its name from lilyth, and the heraldic device emblematic
of this bloodline is the flodily, widely accepted as symbolic of the lily, could not this symbol,
viewed within this context, in fact be the flower of lilyth. The lilyth, say male connection is
also pertinent in regard to the grail saga insofar as the two have a son of their own who seems to
play a recurring role in the whole mythos, as modus.
Not only is Osmodeus the dominant image, shown mirroring Christ, in Renlo Chateau, he is said to have played the central role in building the Temple of Solomon, the edifice from which the Knights Templar took their name.
The recurrence of this strange figure in Grail Law has long perplexed observers, yet it would appear that both he and the descendants of Cain may in fact have shared a kindred ancestry.
It is even said in some traditions that it was as modus whom Moses called upon to part the Red Sea, and not God.
probably see a full ship shaft on live stream,
providing the energy levels,
don't disrupt the wifi at BlackRG.
Oh, the same BlackRG they called you.
Oh yeah, you're the one that called him
so that's just as low as a stupid seagull.
You did say fuckin' that I did look like Jesus
with a Jared Leto thrown in there for some reason.
I mean, I think I'm a little bit cute than Jesus,
but okay, whatever, what's your boat, lady?
I mean, geez, I mean, I've never seen such an insane woman.
I mean, it's like, just like, oh my God.
I mean, it's like, I don't care if I look crazy, really.
I'm not a smith, I'm a cultist, you dingleberry.
I think that is, please.
You're not funny with your milk bone jokes
or your dog bone jokes or, it's not funny.
It's not funny, it's not fun.
In the words of Billy Crystal, okay?
Go lick Lady Bathory's butthole if you want to like talk about like old times, okay?
I'm trying to live in the moment here. Okay. Okay. I'm not I'm just kidding. Okay. I mean, it's like fuck
I'm not in the mood to joke around. I mean
What we got Alice Alice joking with a best friend black RG, right? I mean they're both like these kiwi farms
Low cows. I mean, I'm not on there
They're probably put me on there, but I don't care, but you know what they're
extensively covered on there
Even QE farms find them disgusting, and they're disgusting people QE farm better than mine. I mean, I don't know
I don't know them really but it's like I don't like what they do
But it's like wow what a service they provide for people that are fucking going insane on innocent people like me and the most innocent fucking demon in
Hell, I'm fucking one of the nicest fucking demons you'll ever fucking mean in your entire life
To give me this mad
Not many people do it. Congratulations. Are you happy?
I wish I could I wish I could want my eyes and that can do a better imitation of you be complete
You're heartless. I mean, it's like really it's like I I can't even be as disgustingly heartless as you are alex like really
heartless
innocent people
What's with the n word on my thumbnail?
Well, that's a four. I don't like just nobody. I don't know who that is
She's a she's a fucking
Snobby is fucking porno chick. Why are all these porno chicks and republicans now and understand it
And then what?
Cause so Trump has people to fucking fuck at his rallies.
I don't understand.
What is it?
Alex and fucking Summer Johansson or whatever
that fucking bitch's name was.
I mean, geez.
Pickens are getting slim.
Oh, Jesus.
I can shape shift.
Gonna see me shape shift.
I'll shape shift into a fucking monster.
I'm not gonna turn into a wolf.
I mean, that would require more body hair, okay?
So I'm sure you know something about your waxing bills
probably through the roof.
Sorry, I know I get mean I get mean because I get pushed so far
guys
Have her do this to you and see how you like it. Okay?
This this is this this is Tweedledum
She's basically has less of a brain cell and Tweedledum is is running around thinking she's you know opera or you know
Weatherwoman from Cincinnati, Ohio, you know public access news. Who knows? I mean, it's like
My god, I was a mother in the Cosby show porno. I mean, it's like really you've said that a hundred times
I've heard that you say that I I'm not saying that you say that
That's your claim to fame get another role get a legitimate role
I mean, it's like the Cosby show porno is nothing any of these interested in watching. Oh
I have some pudding pops, but is this like a pudding pudding pop in your pussy. I don't even want to watch that
Jesus Christ
You better be having a guess at the humor about this because it's like geez
If you didn't have a good sense of humor,
then how could you have been a mother
in the Cosme Show porno?
I don't understand.
It just seems like it's something
that someone with a good sense of humor would do.
But you don't have one.
I mean, we're kind of funny making fun of blogger,
but he's such a bitch.
I mean, it's like, nothing else is funny, funny
that you've done.
Yeah, I'm gay.
Of course, I don't have kids, you know, it's like, but,
but yeah, what do your ears say?
Oh, he's, oh, these loser streamers
that are 40s without kids and families.
Look at yourself in the mirror. I mean, come on. I mean, I'm not really mean. I'm just saying it's like, you know
We're in the same boat, you know, you don't have to be so mean and vindictive and cruel. Oh, I say Alex
You know, would you stop you mind stop doxing? You know
Innocent people had nothing to do with any of it, you know. Oh
And I was like, you know, it's like there's a golden rule and stuff. It's not even just in the Bible
It's a kind of universal rule with Buddhism. It's a Hinduism. It's basically like, you know, don't be a fucking asshole
You know, you can't do it. I'll be an asshole. Oh, you don't know what's in my heart
I know it's in your heart bunch of gunk and black oil and shit
Nothing good isn't there. I looked and I looked hard. Oh, did I look oh did I oh my god the excuses I made?
Oh my god, it's just a shadow
Even though I'm covered in oil. It looks like it looks like a fucking bird at a tanker
You know oil leak or whatever
terrible
These other words get a fucking nice, you know, sponge bath with dawn soap. What do I get? Docs!
Oh, my roaches smell so let's take it off. Okay, when someone has peaked on a stranger online, they're massively insecure.
Well, then she must be beyond massive because she's peaked on a lot of strangers online. I mean, here's what she does.
She searches her friend, collects information off she can.
She has spies come out before like Mr. Big Pipes and Mr. Big Poops or whatever and other people come spy on me for
And then she then she accuses me of all this, right? And I never did any of it. She just showed up at my my
I'll play all this. I have all the clips of it. Oh my god
Then even does a Hoover. She has a nerve to Hoover me. Oh, yeah five minutes to get on the panel quick quick quick
Oh, you know, I apologize blah blah blah. Oh, we're all good and then until like brand new queue
Got mad at you even say anything. I'm bad. He called you a bitch or something like that. I mean W Brandon
I mean, it's like I mean if someone had someone had the balls to say at least I mean Jesus Christ
I don't like Brandon. I think he's a scumbag. I think he's like, you know a horrible person, but
You know, I didn't force Brandon on you. I mean, I didn't have any clout with you
I was like, oh my god
She's gonna you know, not even when I talk to me because I talked to him and stuff you come right in and all of a sudden
Oh, can you come on my show and like we're gonna talk Brandon up and stuff and stuff, right?
She played with my fucking feelings like I was a fucking like little toy
This is a sadistic bitch. I mean, I'm sorry. I mean, it's like fuck. She's pulled it out of me
finally
I just fuck with the people I love and then it's like, you know, it's over. I mean, it's really it's like, you know, I
Will die for them
This bitch is not stopping. So she says she has a bullet in her head. Okay
You don't fuck with people's families Alex and I that's what I said in the email to you when I asked very politely asked you
You know, I know you were doxxed in the porn industry when there's a big doxxing in the porn industry
Because you're annoying you bitch. I mean you got banned for a reason if I banned you you're banned for a reason don't ask, okay?
But don't bitch at me
And oh, why are you playing music blah blah blah I'm fucking doing what I want to do
Okay, this is my show get your own fucking show if you want to do your own show
Rogue mod they are hiding you after in the stream. Oh, I think it wasn't me. No, it wasn't road mod. I mean, are you big clips?
That picture that thing is that going for a walk. You're not you're right here. Oh
God, I'm sweating now
This is what happens when the werewolf hormones start to hit. I mean, it's like fucking fuck you Alex. You turn me through a wolf
I mean, congratulations.
I'm gonna fucking go pee on your fucking carpet now.
Fucking take a shit on your couch,
and then fucking leave.
Geez.
I mean, guys, I cannot have been any nicer to this person.
I mean, I was like, I, well, I kissed her ass,
like, you don't know, I'm not stealing cats energy.
I fucking, I know I don't have all this money to like, you know
She says I'm a billionaire or whatever. I'm not so it's like, yeah
She's like you sent me flowers and stuff. Did I ask oh, I need flowers right now
I was in some emergency. No, you sent them on your own. Okay. Oh shut up, Ricky
You can just one time out since it's one time out Ricky, please immediately like mods. I need mods here
People like Ricky using saying if you remember someone says Alice is right
I mean that has to be a retarded person to say that I mean
Can you please, Alex, Doc's Ricky.
I mean, this is like the person that deserves it,
this kind of person.
What did I do to you?
What?
I had Brandon on my show and then you decided to like,
you know, be his best friend, you know, and stuff, right?
I don't understand.
And once you get mad, oh, man, oh,
Sec, you set me up.
I go in the chat and I'm like,
how did I set you up?
What did I do?
Get out of here, you're blocked.
And then I was like, well, what did I do, Alex?
I don't know, text message.
You know what you did.
Who is going for a while that big clips? I don't know who the fuck you are
I mean, I don't care come or come or don't you know
It's like I mean are you a supporter of the show or you just bitching me about meth and shit like that
It doesn't tell you do all your own math. It's just like that was beat it does. I mean geez
You think that's gonna if there's a community on stage
I don't know a comedian or whatever there's a comedian on stage doing a set and having his show and then you say oh
Are you a meth? It just spoils the mood. I'll say right
Why do you keep doing it? I told you to stop doing it a thousand times.
Just stupid. I wish I had some drugs. I need some drugs.
Oh, shut up. Why? I mean, look at, look at you coming on the Alps.
Jose, go, go, go put a hose in your ass. What that?
You're such an n-word, Fifth Sage. Fifth Sage, you're literal n-word.
You're literally, I've seen you. You're darker than Bill Cosby. Out.
Jose. I'm gonna be Mexican so bad.
No, I don't want you to go, but I just don't care if you're like really you know, it's like I mean
It's like yeah, I would love you to love you bird to fit in the show if you're like friendly just rude
And then you go over to kiss me as ass and shit like that. Yeah, so I don't I'm not gonna cry
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna sit here and cry right now about you. I've got this insane porn star fucking
Doing bunch of crazy shit to me. Do you think I have time to like, you know, we're about big clips right now
I mean Jesus Christ
I am a survivor.
I'm like the Destiny's Child song personified
without Kelly Rowland or another bitch.
I'm just Beyonce, okay?
I'm just Beyonce.
Alex is like Beyonce's mother, you know?
Washed up, living off of her daughter's fame.
That was probably the meanest thing I ever said.
Bita has banned Ushima's people who threatened to dox
and send me concrete constantly.
Who are you?
Who is going for a walk?
Who sends you concrete going for a walk?
Who are you?
Are you Bita?
Who are you? You don't get concrete, please you're not important to get concrete
Oh, I'm gonna send I'm gonna send $5 for bag of concrete for going for a walk. There's not even on a stream. Oh
My god, I get threatened
The worst I've been threatened about every single day
I've been threatened to be dismembered and be given AIDS and to you know be killed and left in the ditch
It's almost threatened to send you concrete. They actually send me concrete. You're chatter. Why are you bitching at me? Oh, shut up?
Mean months. I'm trying to compare the threats. Well, that's what you're doing. You're saying well, I'm getting threats
I'm concrete who cares are you getting concrete? I got fucking 40 bags of it
You kissed me his ass in a big lips you do. Oh
Hi, oh, oh, I mean, no, well you kind of do we meet those pictures over that I like but I don't want the picture
You do with me. I'm just saying you're on your own. You're not thin ice, buddy. Okay?
Geez
Okay, guys, so here's what I here's the deal
I have this electric razor, when we start shaving,
I'll do a $5, a line, and we'll start to do my hair too.
This is a pretty strong one too.
It looks weak, but it's strong.
Vita, here's the curve Vita's ahead of.
Vita's ahead of the bush, okay?
Because her bush, it pokes out,
can't be in front of her, her hedge maze
in front of her house, okay?
That's the only thing I care about,
you know, that she trims her bush.
You know BMI be ahead of the curve, but you're you're you're stomped onto the curve you and we're out
I mean, I these people I just can't stand it. We're back. What a night. Oh
What night?
with internet drama
Usually, a feud between two creators ends with a few angry videos and a block button.
But in a specific corner of YouTube, these personal disagreements are handled differently.
They end with an exorcism.
Take a recent morning update from a live streamer named Alexandra.
She didn't log on to simply vent about a rival creator named John, known as Psych.
She logged on to announce she had successfully called upon divine intervention to purge a
The conflict escalated because Alexandra accused John of being an active practitioner of goetic magic.
According to her, John was running operations straight out of the occult manuals of Aleister Crowley,
invoking dark forces to drain energy from rival streamers.
The specific diagnosis was that John was possessed by Asmodeus.
In theological lore, Asmodeus is a notorious prince of hell, associated with lust and wrath.
Alexandra claimed this exact entity was entirely responsible for John's toxic behavior in the chatrooms.
To counter this, Alexandra deployed a targeted spiritual defense.
She officially called upon the Archangel Raphael to perform a digital exorcism,
stating that the angel would now be monitoring John indefinitely to ensure Asmodeus could never return.
In these communities, aesthetics that usually serve as hobbies, like tarot cards and astrological symbols,
are treated as literal tactical weapons.
You don't just read the cards, you use them to block incoming digital hexes.
So if someone annoys you in a stream, you don't cancel them.
You reframe their annoyance as a demonic attack, turning an otherwise standard YouTube
argument into a high-stakes theological war.
Alexandra claims once a demon's glamour is removed, a person's core energy is finally
exposed.
For John, she argues that this core isn't human, but a latent, aggressive canine energy
that had been suppressed for years by his occult practice. The community diagnostic is that John
is a shapeshifter. Specifically, he is currently woolsing out and transitioning into a canine
cryptid right on camera. To prove this, viewers began analyzing his lifestreams frame by frame.
They pointed to his heavier jawline and his brow ridge shifting as evidence of an active, real-time biological mutation.
The ultimate domestic proof came from John's own pets.
Viewers claimed that his cats, who normally sat with him on stream, were suddenly hiding off-camera,
supposedly terrified of the aggressive new canine energy radiating from their owner.
The community has moved past invisible spiritual infections.
focusing instead on the physical evolution of a man they believe is literally transforming
behind his webcam. In this corner of the internet, these werewolves are treated as the intentional
products of a hidden infrastructure. Enter figures like Nathan Reynolds, an ex-military
whistleblower who frequently appears in the community's expanded universe. He ties these
claiming his own family used occult practices to build a massive tobacco and industrial empire.
According to this lore, these elites collaborate with the government inside deep underground
military bases, easing sites like the Cheyenne Mountain Complex for black magic operations.
The natural geography of Colorado is cited as a strategic hotspot.
Locations like the Garden of the Gods are described as cardinal points
making it the perfect hub for high-level witchcraft and interdimensional gateways.
Inside these remote facilities, the military allegedly communes directly with reptilian entities
and genetically spliced wolf people who emerge from subterranean tunnels to receive offerings.
By linking John to these facilities,
his personal transformation becomes a single data point in a much larger project,
A sprawling, deep-state matrix that supposedly manufactures and monitors these creatures.
But if you actually log in to one of John's live streams, the apocalyptic mythology instantly
collapses.
Instead of practicing goetic magic or receiving encrypted deep-state orders, John is usually
just sitting at his desk, arguing with Chad about Marvel Comics and giving lukewarm takes
The terrifying canine energy and bloody attacks referenced by rivals
trace back to incredibly normal events,
like John telling a story about his pitball
getting a minor scratch on its nose from another dog at the local park.
Stripped of its occult filter,
this entire saga is standard internet bickering.
It's a handful of isolated people trading insults,
misinterpreting mundane life events,
and getting genuinely angry over chatroom slides.
Building such an elaborate mythology transforms a mundane afternoon in a chat room into a cosmic
struggle. It gives every viewer a reason to believe their time spent in a stream is actually a
contribution to a global defensive effort. The human instinct to create epic myths didn't
vanish with the ancient world. We didn't stop believing in monsters and magic,
we just updated the venue. We are still actively writing folklore, complete with demons, angels,
right in the middle of YouTube live streams.
Okay, I apologize for losing my temper again. You know, I
don't like to do that. I would love to have a nice conversation.
Well, I'll let you talk first because you're more wordy than I am.
Okay, I'll just say in my opinion, in the way I see things, and maybe you see things differently,
I don't feel like I did anything
wrong or even bad bad to you when you turn on me the second time and I know
that there's some people were saying some of my show I did necessarily know
what's true and what's not true at that point and I was defending you all I
could and took to one point until you went too far with me
And I try it again to be polite and like politely ask you because it's like, you know, I do think that there is good in you
I don't think you're a bad person. I think and I don't even think porn is bad. It's like, I mean, I'm not against porn
I mean, I've said things to try to hurt you, right? It's like because I get triggered and hurt
I mean, it's like and maybe you've done the same thing. I know those people we know that do the same thing
Okay, we have your emotional people sometimes
but
I just, he's been so far with me, I was like, I mean, it's like, I just, it just seemed almost, almost like, you know, unbelievably evil, but you know, I don't want to come at you, you know, angry, I don't want to come at you mad.
I don't think you're a bad person. You were, when we got along, we got along fine. I mean, it's like, I mean, pretty much 90% of the time when we were friends, we didn't have an issue at all.
And so it's just frustrating.
It turns on a dime at a certain time.
And then it's ramping up a little bit, it seems, too.
And it's like, so I don't feel like getting on the ride again,
because it's like, you know, it's like, I don't want to have you back to me.
You can say, if you would like to,
I don't want to communicate with you anymore.
But that, I mean, you've come to a point where it's like, I mean,
it's like, that's almost like, you know, but the thing is,
In your Capricorns you understand. Let me just say this. Well, let's forget about what wait. Let's let's pause
Yeah, let's forget about astrology
Yeah, it's all that kind of stuff. Sure. Um, I'll just say one thing that
The Capricorns are very loyal once they love somebody they don't stop loving the person
Even if they end up like, you know, really not liking them at all
Like once someone has like the heart, it's like it's not like so easy for us to like give it up like that, right?
And I really did care for you. I really did. I was such a cheer. I mean, I think
You don't have to care about me anymore
But but don't make it so I don't mean it's like you almost tried to sabotage it and that's frustrating too
Like it's like cuz you didn't have to do that. Um psych. Yeah, I have a question for you. Sure
have you encountered this sort of cycle with other people before I've been
through narcissistic abuse cycles with other people but it's plus California
there's a lot of narcissists here so let's even forget about the construct of
narcissism let me ask you a few questions and you don't have to answer if
it's uncomfortable or you just don't want to answer okay I'm happy to answer
who have been very honest about a level of hypocrisy that you embody?
Well, honest about, so long term friends that say I'm a total hypocrite and everything's my fault basically, right?
Take it as you will just answer how you asked to see this is what you do with the AI you like frame it. I'm not AI
I'm I'm a person. Yes, you did. There's no way to answer the poll about me without a big and negative answer towards me
It was like why does it do that?
It's my poll. Calm down. Calm down. Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
Every answer was bad. There's no, there's no time limit. I'm giving you all the time you would like to talk to me in the world today. Okay. Okay.
I did a poll for myself recently. I said, do I deserve to live? And it was like 47% said no. You do deserve to live. That's not a question.
I hope you live. I hope you outlive me. You're younger than I am. You should.
Well, you know, we're through some more age. I mean, I don't want it. I don't want anyone to die, you know
It's like I wouldn't everyone let's not let's move away from death. We don't want to talk about death. Okay
Let's let's forget that
um
When it comes to what you have done that has hurt me from my perspective
extensively I
Confide it in you some personal things which you've disclosed to the public. Okay?
Wow. Stop. Stop. Stop.
The examples. No, I'm not giving you examples. I'm just answering and I'm tired.
Absolutely. Okay, so you don't want me to talk.
I do. I do, but I want to have a conversation though. I just want to say you.
I'm trying to. You're not letting me talk.
Okay, good. Right here.
Do you have any sort of beer or anything right now?
I have a pineapple passion.
All right. Well, I'm going to have a drink with you. Let's do that first, please.
Well bottoms up. All right. Cheers
Someone's asking what I'm wearing
It's actually a Japanese style top. I'm wearing some jean shorts right now
all right
for all of you with a level of
Autism and curiosity you know what I'm wearing. Okay
now
Also, I disclose to you certain people in these communities. I want zero connection with and I told you why
and you immediately, and I know why you did it,
but let me finish, and then you can counter,
but let me finish, I think you did it
as a way to gain leverage over me,
maybe have a level of control,
and I don't appreciate that.
That's why I have permanently taken some steps back from you.
I'm not saying that you're the worst of the worst
for connecting with certain people
that I've told you are detrimental to me, but you did it.
You also brought me into a situation to where because I trusted you and I'm talking about the Brandon situation
But then you kind of threw me under the bus with that. I didn't like that
So those are really the main three things now when it comes to how I view you
I think you're a beautiful person. You know, I think that about you. I think you're extensively creative
I think you're smart as a whip
I think you have so much potential. I don't like how you think of yourself.
I don't like how you mistreat yourself, but I also have realized that you do
have a lack of awareness when it comes to how you treat others who have treated you well.
I think you have a lot of people around you who are enablers or who are essentially yes people,
Certain things, and I'm not saying I haven't hurt you. I'm a certain kind of person. I will, I'm to the death.
I told you that from the beginning, okay? But I think that I might be too mature to really be the kind of friend that should be your absolute best friend.
That's what I think.
and I want you to know I don't hate you.
I see so much in you.
You're an amazing person, and you know this.
You know how I think, come on now.
But when it comes to certain things,
I'm not going to back down because prior in my life there were a lot of things I turned blind eye to a lot of things
I've backed down from and I can't be that person anymore not considering certain
Responsibilities I have certain things that I've gone through things along those lines. So that's really
I think what I need it to put in your head.
Okay.
And that's it.
But now feel free to say whatever you want
cause you got all the time in the world
when it comes to me.
Okay.
And I want to, you know, of course, like, you know,
if you want to jump in it too,
if I do have a point and stuff like that, you go ahead.
But I just want to say at the, I didn't know Brandon,
like, you know, when he came in,
I didn't really know the story, you know,
it was dumb enough to think maybe he was even like, you know,
kind of like Latina so I don't know maybe it was like when the bad boys club thing the AI of him was
cute or something I don't know because I didn't use you like I was like what was I thinking you
know sometimes we do things we're like what the fuck was I thinking that's what happened with me
with Brandon and it's like you know I was being rebellious because I had a bunch of people telling
me oh don't don't do this or do this and I don't like to be told what to do you know you know that
It was a surprise to me like all of a sudden I heard oh Alice is talking about you and
writing brands on your show and I was like oh shit and you're like oh it's like he hosting
predators then you came over we had a good conversation.
I do have to interrupt.
Why do you do your show if it makes you so upset?
Well because I know I already know the answer but I want to hear your answer really.
Because I like to be alive, you know, I like to feel alive sometimes.
But you are alive and I think that you need more differentiation from being on here and
off of here.
My criticism of you is that this, and it's okay if this, it happens with the best of
entertainers, method acting.
and in a weird sort of way, I've directed you to an extent,
and I do know what I'm doing when I do it.
And you like being directed to an extent,
because I do know you very well,
but you should direct yourself.
If this is truly your ship, all yours,
then you shouldn't accept so much external input.
But if you do need external input,
Then you got to be willing to submit to that external input
Okay. Yeah, well, you know, I'm told a billion a billion things by chat
I mean a lot of it is trolling it's like I have to learn the difference and differentiation who I can trust and who's well
You wrote a book on troll now. Can I ask you a serious? And you don't have to answer
Did you let the A.I. write that book or did you write that book?
Listen, the A.I. did a big grammar check and formatting a little bit.
Did it create the outline?
Not the outline. No, I created the outline.
I created the outline and it, you know, some things...
Were filled in a little bit with it. I it was very minimal with that book because I know everyone's looking at it
I read the book. I think I bought the book. Yeah, I like I mean the book
I mean the thing is like just like I was talking to Vanguard yesterday and he said
I was telling my family, you know, ancestry, and I was like, yeah, pagans and, you know,
druids and vikings.
And he's like, you don't have vikings here.
And I was like, well, yeah, I do.
It's part of my DNA.
I don't, maybe I don't look like a viking or I'm not going to go bridging pillage me.
You are starting to.
Well, maybe I am in the Eric the Red or something like that.
I don't know.
I do have no region in me, like 10%.
I know.
Probably more than that.
Yeah.
I do have some bikey, but he was like, no, you don't.
And I was like, what the fuck are you telling me?
He probably doesn't have, I mean, then it looks like.
Why do you care with the only person
who knows what you are as you?
I know, I know.
But it's just like, there's a fact that he's just like,
so dismissive.
I hate within this, like, that's the thing.
It's like, I don't, I'm, I know who I am.
I don't have anything to prove, but I'm so mis.
labeled. I don't think you've taken the time to get to know who you are now. I think maybe
you knew who you were 20s, maybe 30s. Now, I'm 47, so you're what, 45? Or something
like that? Okay. It's hard for men when they're around your age, okay? Right. And
That's why I was saying before maybe and I'm not saying you have to take a nap right now
I actually want to talk to you right now. Yeah, but um
You do tend to
um
act
For a long period of time
Let it go, but then you're upset about the reaction to your actions
And that's where you got to have a little bit more confidence if you truly are confident in what you're doing.
Okay.
But maybe you're not confident in what you're...
Everybody has...
How do you really feel about your show now?
I feel that...
It's a good show. I feel like that it's good content
I feel like people are interested in it even people that say they hate me are interested in it and like to talk about it and come
And watch it. I mean, it's like if they didn't like it. They wouldn't be they just like it be this as she hates me
I'm a piece of shit in there, but I'm not irrelevant to her because
She's watching my show when she's watching her show when she's doing her show. She's watching my show
I've grown to like Vita. We don't talk behind the scenes. We're not friends. I've just grown to like her
And what I want you to think about is why has it been difficult for you to give her
a solid break from you and you would break from her,
but why has that been difficult for you?
I have for months at a time.
Well, like she wasn't even on my show.
It hasn't been months at a time I've tracked it.
Well, because I mean, it's like,
I occasionally will go to her show,
but it's like I'll get triggered hearing her talk about me
and I'll, I don't know, I'll chat to her.
Okay, now let's pause there.
Yeah, yeah.
So how do you think that makes others feel when you do the same?
You've done that to me not only on your panel, but on other people's panels too.
You've done what? What are you thinking exactly?
Talk about the person that might want distance from you,
but you're talking about them and it's triggering them,
so you're putting out to others what you're receiving that you know is hurtful.
Well, look at this was the balloon chat says no no
No, no stop
Talk about the chat. Did you hear what I just said take that off the screen, please? I'm trying to be okay
What I just said yeah was what beta does that you explained hurts you
You do to others
Do you think that?
You're hurting others to the same capacity or on a same parallel because I'm gonna tell you right now. You are
Yeah, well, right
Okay, well, let me just say
Does she fucking talk about me every day for hours? Yes
And it's like yes
I like to respond when people are calling me an animal abuser and people are saying all the horrible things about me and in lies
I mean, I have like a human thing where I don't like it and
Thing that is, you're about to get fucking banned, too.
You don't tell me what to do, okay?
I'll ban who I want.
Don't fucking tell me what to do, okay?
That's the number one rule here.
Don't tell me what to do.
Let's switch gears,
because I'm curious about something.
Is your relationship with thing a friendship
or in the romantic realm?
He's a beat-a-bit liquor.
I mean, I love things like this, but he's just,
he's for beat-a.
Well, it's a question, is it platonic?
or is it slightly romantic with you?
I'm not talking about V, I'm talking about you.
I'm not attracted to, you know.
I'm not sitting, is he attracted to you?
That's, anything's possible.
I'm not gonna put him in that position where I think that.
I want your cock gamble.
I don't know, you're a little bit too feminine for me.
I'm sorry.
I like more masculine guys gambling.
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to distract you by the chat. I'm not gonna look at the chat
I'm just gonna look at you. Hold on. I'm gonna close it right there. There we go. It's close. I'm not even looking at it. I apologize.
Well, let's have another drink.
Do I have any coffee? Okay. I am oppressed out of alcohol, but bottoms up.
You don't have to have alcohol if you don't want to. Don't make me drink.
I would love some, but I just don't have any. It's okay.
I don't know, I have a lot of, this isn't,
it's like, I have stress, the show is-
You have a lot of, you have a lot of stress
and I think that you put a lot of stress
upon you, yourself, natelessly.
Yeah.
I'm hard on myself than anybody else is.
I mean, that's why I can kind of like,
deal with most of the stuff,
because it's like, I say worse things
than anybody else could say,
and think worse things than anybody else could say.
So, but at the same time,
I do know myself and I do, like, have a certain level of self-love and self-confidence, and
I've been by myself my whole life, like, the thing is, it's like, I didn't...
No, you haven't.
Okay, listen, I had a little brother, a little sister I grew up with, and, you know, and my
mom and dad.
And so that was like, you know, we were, you know, every Sunday and stuff, but as for
...
other things like no I was I wasn't like very up until high school I would I
kind of started partying in high school I wasn't you know barely out of the house
out a lot of the house until I was 15 I didn't get my car until I was 18
And so I was pretty much, and I was in a city where there's a bunch of
Do you understand how blessed you are to have had a car at 18?
A lot of people don't have that, man.
Sure, I know, but you know what?
I feel my driver says five times in a row, behind the wheel test.
You know, it's like, I mean, I worked hard for that license.
I would have probably had it sooner if I hadn't like, you know, in such a fuck-up.
But, you know, I do have a nervous thing where I get under pressure, I get nervous sometimes.
I understand I've been blessed and I understand a lot of people aren't blessed and a lot of people are maybe more or less
I don't really compare myself in that way because we don't choose our parents
You know our parents kind of like or maybe we do spiritually. I'm not sure but we don't choose our parents
We don't choose where we're born. I have there's a lot of things that you chose good a good
Environment, it's but I think no matter what environment you chose you would still be the same
Disatisfied, but it's not the external
mm-hmm. It's
internal when it comes to you, and I'm not insulting you by saying that you just have
a ways to go.
And it's interesting to me because you are very smart, extremely so, in some capacities,
but you're closed off, and I think that you close yourself off from things that you don't
want to hear.
That's some I've had to work on that and I'm definitely not where I probably should be
But I am a little bit older than you are and I've lived a little bit more of life than you have and I'm not saying
exceedingly amount of life more than you but I have
And I don't like seeing you in pain. Okay, that's what I will say. Okay, okay because I do see I see you trying
I'm not going to say that you don't try, but you could try harder.
I think also you immediately, when you're not good at something, you write it off instead
of trying harder, and that's something that I think you need to work on, truly.
Whether I agree with everything you say or not, you know
I know you're speaking from your heart and it's like and you really you do believe it
Yeah, and so it's like and I appreciate your can't your candor and your
honesty with that and so and also
What I'll say for myself is I try, I don't even try.
I am just myself as much as I can be.
It's like, and I've put myself out there
and embarrassing and ugly and ridiculous situations
and even on purpose sometimes, sometimes.
So I can like, you know, get over some of my,
when I started doing my show,
I had to be so drunk in order to turn on my camera.
I was so shy.
I'm a shy person in real life.
I don't-
I've met you in real life.
I guess you forgot.
I remember. I remember. I know exactly how you are. You are completely an introvert and that's
where you're out of balance because you shouldn't be. Yeah and I've been really. What do you think
led you to be that way honestly? I had well I went to like you know um my six years old
kid I was pretty small school and I was kind of like you know not the most popular. I was kind of
a weird kid I guess like you know my elementary school age I was like you know just you know
Um, but, uh, what was it?
I mean, it's like, I basically, I found some kind of level of popularity in high school.
I had some fun and it's like, and I kind of feel like I wasted my 20s and 30s.
I, I wish I would have like put my, done something good.
I mean, I, I've had a.
I've had a good job before and stuff.
I've had it for two years.
I was an employee of the month, several months
and several months and stuff.
I mean, I've had some levels of success,
but it's like, as for, then I just think,
oh, this will have to last forever.
I have to get up at this time forever.
I can't, I don't like to wake up at a certain time.
I don't like to wake up early.
I hate early things, so.
So, you don't like schedules,
and you don't like constructions.
Yeah.
I sent you my final,
thing over I'm ever gonna send you because you do need some drinks whether you drink them tonight or not
They'll be over there. Thank you. I appreciate that. I know and I don't want you to be
To feel alone. I don't want you to feel sad
But at the same time, I don't want you to think that you can walk all over people in
Disregard their feelings because you do tend to do that
Right, and I'm all I say is like in relationships. It's like I feel like sometimes I'm kind of like I'm
very receptive person like a very
Almost like a mirror sometimes where I'm just like I'm very like if I get into a conflict with somebody
90% of the time I'm just mirroring them back at me. Let's pause mirror or appeaser
I feel like naturally, I'm near.
Like, and you saw, like, when you touched your hair,
I touched my hair.
I mean, it's like, I don't know if I learned that
from one of your comments.
You don't.
Yeah.
But yeah, I just, like, I've been-
I think you learned it from your parents, personally.
And I'm not dissing your parents at all.
I think they did what they thought that they should do
with you.
I know mine did, and they definitely were far from perfect.
No one's perfect.
But I think that you're naturally an appeaser,
and you've learned over the years how to appease people.
I like you're appeasing me right now. You don't even realize keep the peace. I like I love
Peace I love but to what consequence within
Because you do have to say what's on your mind because otherwise it's gonna kill you because it's gonna build up inside of you
It's gonna be on your shoulders or wherever it is that you hold it within and eventually you're gonna have a heart attack from it
Yeah
Well, and I I mean I have a few people I can talk to like now and like you and you were one of them
And it's like I love talking to you and I said we had good conversations and talked about everything and you know
And I have a few and I've very there's very few people that people can do that with right?
It's like I could count them on like less than three fingers probably I don't talk to my family that often
You know, I so my friends that will actually like talk to me or and I are interested in me and like love me
I mean I treasure I treasure them and I I treasure I mean I treasure you I mean I still I still do
I mean no matter what it's like
Well, I don't need to be treasured by anybody. I treasure myself the treasure appreciate or
I see you haven't appreciated because because there were like I I went down the list of what I felt you did
Which are all very major things at least and I'll even write them down. I'll send you a uh
You know a file
for you to look at because I would like for you to actually be able to visibly see it. I'll email
or text it to you, whatever. I want you to have it in concrete terms so that with other people,
and I'm not saying that you can never talk to me again. We're not going in that direction at this
You're dismissive sometimes you forget sometimes because you're very in the present
you do tend to be a lot in the past and
You have you do you're also in the future you think about all these plans you have sometimes they manifest sometimes they don't
Yeah, but I
Mean in a strange way as much as you complain
about your immediate present and your surroundings.
I think in a strange way,
you do seek out people that can help you,
but you're not always happy with the answers you receive.
Like right now, okay, let's see.
You have 47 people in your chat,
and I'm saying that that's a high number.
But...
It's a certain number right now of quality people who are actively participating because
you're being real, real.
And how did you get to the point of being real, real?
through the adversity, through the challenges,
through really having someone say to you,
hey, fuck you, I'm not gonna submit to you.
You do have a very natural, dominant personality,
you don't wanna admit it, and you trick people
by acting like a little pussycat,
but then that's why I've been equating,
metaphorically, the wolf thing.
You're a wolf boy, you don't wanna admit it,
but you fucking are, cause I've seen it before.
I do like and you're afraid of that.
I heard you when I was in the car driving
and doing some errands today.
I never knew that you had dogs before
and you were talking about the loyalty of dogs.
I heard you reflect that when you were yelling at me before
talking about Capricorn, equating that to loyalty.
You shouldn't equate any of that to anything.
Right.
But what I am saying is that I came to realize
about you today.
that you do need a level of unconventional love,
a level of loyalty, but you can't expect that naturally
from everybody, especially if you're willing
to breach certain boundaries,
that that person might not show hurts them.
Like, look, I don't show everything.
I know you think I'm a terrible actress.
Thank God.
You're a good actress, but-
No, I'm terrible.
But what I will say is that I'm good at
masking hurt, because I've had to.
I can't let everybody know exactly how I feel.
And I haven't shown you, or even told you exactly how I feel.
But I'm telling you now, you do have a tendency
of not listening at times, because you're
so thinking about what you're going to say later
that you don't always.
And maybe that works for you.
I don't really know.
But it can be hurtful.
Certain people not just myself, but others have needed to disconnect from you because you do replace people very quickly too
Or at least you attempt to
Well, I know I mean I know like you know there have been situations where I've kind of like, you know
Got jumped on that hate tape on train. The thing is what you said it makes this makes sense to me
Okay, and I I mean I accept what you're saying and Alex and I accept that as your truth and stuff what I would what I would have liked
when that situation happened
was rather than
You instantly do a live and say, oh, you know, it's that keep me training and then when I talk in chat
You block me and then I write you a text message. What did I do?
You're like, well, it's my platform then and especially considering that you've treated me a certain way
I know you do you don't want to acknowledge certain things you delete certain things and I just happen to catch it
It's all on it's on rumble everything's on rumble my whole show every so I don't yeah, there's things I've noticed
I'm just very quick. You're not used to
Someone who's cool. I know you're quick. I know you're quick. I know you're short for this attack
Like you know in a good way, but here's what I'm saying is that
And not beyond the show and stuff like that because I was whatever you could do a show about whatever you want
Whatever you want about whatever you want and don't you don't have to have to be in the chat or whatever
But when I did text you after and I was like Alice I was like Alex
What's going on how you blocked so I don't know if I got a text from you got that first one the first one
You can do it and you and I said but I said what did I do?
And you kind of respond to what you know what you did and I was like well
That's just feel it like kind of gaslight a little bit because I don't know what I did
It could have been a million things that like so I didn't know I was like
it was that day with Brandon and stuff and I was like, you know, you're like, well, can someone go
over talk to Brandon, calm him down. And I was like, okay, I know when and then just so that you're
aware, not communicating with that person anymore. Okay, he's back from my show. You know, I had my
own differences with him too. And it's like, but I mean, also we did have some discussions about
you're like, well, I don't really care.
If you have these people as mods or friends or whatever
You're like just don't bring me into it or force me to be friends with them
And I really did make an effort not to ever do that
But I do know that there was a lot of people that you didn't care for and they really didn't care for and probably put up with
A lot that you didn't express to me. I'm the kind of person to where if I'm friends with a person
I know this is very selfish on my part. I
Have to and I just know this about myself. I
Have to have privacy
I have to be the one when it comes to that interaction.
And that's what I require, and I'm tool to change.
And that's my flaw.
I'm flawed tremendously.
I will not deny that, OK?
Well, the best thing about it is that you're going to.
I'm telling you.
If you have some inner awareness about it,
and so you know you're flawed, and that's
half of the battle with it, then you
can decide to work on it or not, or whatever you want.
But you have an awareness.
would have talked more about not to gather information but in order so I didn't do something
wrong because I'm very sometimes thoughtless right I I'm very my mind works very fast and
abstract in certain ways and so it goes in all different places and stuff and so I'll say things
and I trigger a lot of people I piss off a lot of people and not even trying that's why I'm
Some men have like this kind of latent sexuality in them, you know, and that I trigger and I'm
Why are you so fixated on that particular element that you just mentioned?
The what with men oh straight straight men or just men straight men and exploring
Because you can sway them in a certain direction because I'm not very attracted to like feminine men
And so that like leaves like either the closet in men or just like the super like butch
Out gay guys that are usually they're in hiding at some point in their life in between there
So I have a very small dating pool. I don't know what it is. Also. It's like the challenge. Also. It's like
Also, I really was not into like, I mean, like the sex, it was just like, it was better in my mind than it was like in real life, and I was always disease phobic, you're up in the 80s and just always seeing this negative stuff about it and disease and people dying and stuff.
So it was kind of like I was very disease phobic. And so I'm not really.
Especially in California because yeah, and in the gay community, too
I mean, it's like there's I mean basically I could hook up with a different person every single day of my life
I wanted to like even if I was like ten times uglier and you know, the gray hair I could still do that
I mean, that's like the gay community. I mean, that's gay people are
sometimes
Yeah, easier to hook up with I don't know if it's like if I wanted to let's pause
Because I'm gonna go outside and have a cigarette. I didn't smoke indoors. I want you to well don't walk to the store
I'm something over
Well, I sent you a 12 pack over. Oh, thank you. Oh my god. You sent it to my house. Thank you so much
Yeah, yeah, and I'll tell you they're they're in the checkout process. It should be their
Let's see. I'm not sure the time changed. What time is it right where you are? It is seven thirty nine
So it'll be there in like
20 minutes
It says like a window of 20 minutes to an hour, but it's probably going to be like between 20 and 30 minutes
Can you wait? Yes. Oh, yeah, I don't need to. Yeah, that way you don't have to go to the store. Yes, perfect
Thank you so much. You're welcome. All right, I'm gonna go outside. I'm a cigarette
Maybe somebody else wants to come up take me down. Okay, the black RG wants to come up
Maybe think that is wants to come up who else is in the chat? Oh, look at the chat
Maybe I don't know who else would want to come up, but maybe some of you want to share your thoughts
Maybe you want to counter my thoughts. This is kind of the
psych
wolf
Therapy night in a roundabout way Q&A night fuck therapy Q&A
Q&A before he wolfs out tomorrow night. I'm sticking to that
Okay. Well, I hope I'm like, I hope my hair, I hope I'm really hairy and it looks good and it doesn't look, it doesn't look too good.
Well, maybe it'll look amazing. You never know.
We are actually theatrical. You never know, but I mean, give me about 15 to 10 minutes.
You got it. You got it. Thank you. All right.
Okay.
Sigsel.
Hey, are you completing your, are you going to morph into a wolf werewolf after you get your 12 pack?
Look how much you ain't seen much hair like Chester. I have like this is how much I can't turn into a wolf with that
I mean, that's too sad. I mean, I need like I need like a rug
I mean, I need I didn't the first of all I need to hair over the tattoos. No one can see it
We could also get like
Well, you know like thumbtacks. Yeah, I can get thumbtacks
I could I could actually get a real rug and just thumbtack it in my chest. How about you just get like minoxidil?
Yeah, minoxidil for like ball
No, I don't want to hear about ball. I'm evolving. I don't want to hear about pink thumbtacks into my chest of the rug
Okay, it's not the time to say you left. Okay. Okay. Oh, he's still here say
Don't do that's the minoxidils. Okay. Okay. Shut up. Okay. I don't I can't take it
I'll put I'll put on a video here. This is the new introduction to the show. Enjoy it here
Welcome to the cult of psyche
Please take a lantern
Sanitize your mirror and remember
This is not a real cult
Our dental plan is terrible
I showed up late to the first gate The Sphinx said, buddy, you're a, that's confirmation
by a Zindis guy The cult master wore a velvet cape
Bearers have seen things up The open panel starts at 9 by 9 0 5
We've left space-time A wizard argues young with chatter
Cryptid's microphone sounds bad A troll arrives to just debate
The new interrupts for 48 consecutive minutes
What a-
The shadow volume says hit delete
Someone cries the earth is flat
Someone else has proved the cat
The cat will come to the cult
They're on your cleaning
The ectoplasm machine
No military reply, I need more proof
Wonder yelled a glowing sphere
Discernment said that's ball chandelier
Transformation grew new wing
The library has every text
But nobody knows which book is next The rituals are strictly voluntary
Except returning books to the library To guard your freedom, mind and growth
I'll never have to to obey Music absolutely slaps
So sing my name's chaotic And your application to become
under review
I was about to play the wolf among us. I actually had that game
I was about to play it, but I couldn't get it to share the screen sick
I'll let you up. I just want to play when we're strong and then I'll let you up when I'm
Probably I'll expect
I am asking your help
in the tremendous task of informing and alerting the American people
But we are opposed around the world by a monolithic and ruthless conspiracy
and relies primarily on public means, on infiltration, instead of invasions.
And of all the men in the world, and of all the powers made, what's the point?
What's the end goal?
And you said the end goal is to engage the chip, to control the whole society.
That was irreversible. This was not an election. This was a revolution. This was irregular warfare at its finest.
We have what we call citizen journalists. We have an army of digital soldiers.
You're here because you've made a decision about something in your life.
Thank you. Anyone still here? I'm here. Here I am. Hi, I was sickest here too. I mean,
oh, he left. He left. Okay, come back. All right, I'm still here. Okay, fix my face.
Yeah, I played the Isaac Cappy song because, you know, he was like a little bit almost like,
you know, he was a little bit behind, but he's a little bit ahead of this time, too. Like,
And in 2016, there was like, you know, Facebook groups,
oh, join the Illuminati, we'll give you a car
and a house, blah, blah, blah.
He thought those were real and stuff.
He thought Seth Green or Seth Rogan had like a,
he had a bookcase to cover in his bedroom
so people wouldn't go in there and like use the bathroom
and snort coke in there when they had a party and stuff.
Oh, really?
And he's like, this is where we keep the children.
And then Isaac believed him and thought he was like, um,
was he telling the truth or was he lying?
I think he was lying.
I think it was just his master bedroom, but he, but he's like,
this is where the children kept any, he said it in a real weird way.
Do you only focus on like kind of dark stuff?
Or do you ever listen to like happy stuff or uplifting things?
Like I am like this, wow, I love everything from like, you know, Nightmare on the Street
to a Disney movie when I was a kid, right?
It's like, I mean, I just like, I'm all over the place really.
It's like, I don't know anything.
I don't know what role it gives me for what reason, but it's, I don't know.
Can I do a song request?
I'm going to put something backstage.
It's not going to be up your alley.
It's not going to be up your audience's alley.
It's not going to give you a copyright strike or anything.
It's an AI song, so you might like it.
I like your music.
Well, I didn't make this.
totally AI. I like the variety song you played. Well that was Reform Stoic and that was not AI.
Reform Stoic has amazing music but this is biblically inspired. Your audience isn't going
to like it. I apologize to your audience in advance but maybe just to hear something a little different.
Yeah, there you go. It's uh, I guess it's uploading. I don't know. I think I see it. Here we go. All right, just say
Chronicles 29. So yeah, that's where I am in the Bible right now.
I did what I like mentioned about you know, because I know I don't think I know it's not your style
I know it's not your I forced you to listen to it. I actually like I will tell you like
I don't know how much I talked about and your delivery is almost there. You're gonna have to show your ID just
All right, thank you so much.
Like, you know, when I was a kid,
like my family wasn't religious, you know,
they're kind of the worldly people, you know,
it's like they, you know.
They probably introduced you,
but weren't like a hundred percent in.
Yeah.
They were like, I mean,
they're not like church goers and stuff.
My grandma, my grandma was kind of,
but you know, we did have a church stuff
and pretty nice church right on like the ocean and stuff.
It takes being worldly to create the churches, to be honest with you.
Right.
Later on, there's one more song, but not right now because I don't want to annoy your audience
or anything, but the other song that I recently made has specifically to do with what we're
about to talk about, how it takes being worldly and collaborating with other people who are
push the spirituality in whatever direction it is that whatever group it is, you know,
is part of or see fit. But it's, it's, it's a weird, difficult balancing act between spirituality
and the capacity to keep it going when you really think about it because the only way you can keep
You're of the material world and then the people who choose to be of the opposite of that world
They benefit from it, but then they might go against the material world and then vice versa
So it's always a struggle. Yeah, and you know spirituality is like, you know, it's up
I mean, the world is a spiritual place.
So I mean, even though we're here for a limited amount of time
and we live and die here and things like that,
the world goes on with us, with us here or not.
And we carry the light for a period
just like the Olympic torch people, right?
That's kind of something reminding me of like,
you know, if you're carrying the light,
everything comes from like the one, right?
And we're all part of this one.
And so it's like a duality,
but it's also a singularity too.
we live in the apparent duality but it's like when it all comes down to it we're all it's all
connected and interconnected with everything and so um also if people don't have hard experiences
like they probably wouldn't look to god or really i mean it's like you know sometimes it's not till
something that both you and i have gone through that wakes us up and makes us conscious of the other
Some people they never feel that when you lose somebody close to you. You do you do feel them at least I have and
Some people if they haven't gone through that they don't know till later. It's kind of called the death club
Not everybody is a part of the death club and I don't want people to be a part of the death club is horrible, but
Maybe it's not so horrible. Maybe it's just another
facet that opens
to you that it can hurt, but it does elevate you to an extent.
The only thing that makes it okay is that we all go through, we will all go through like the, we all die, you know, like eventually, right?
Everybody, it's like, I mean, even if we have an internal soul and things like that.
And in this body, we have a limited time on this earth.
That also gives us the opportunity to like, want to live and do things because we have a limited time.
just like kind of God. I think God got bored just like being alone in the
universe and just being everything. And he went into like experience other
things and so kind of split himself apart like a mirror, like a broken mirror
or something. All these reflections of them that were like apparently
different, but really the same source, but able to interact and learn and
actually grow.
Someone just said something in your chat that
I had to stop myself from laughing because I didn't want you to think I was laughing at you because I'm not but it was so
insightful
First I'm gonna read it first contact five nine three four says
Psych is streaming on the other side of good times green screen
To an extent to an extent
Many of you out there who followed me for a very long time, you know, I have an affinity for good times. I care about him
I care about this one, too. I do
I'll put in the time sometimes
Sometimes it doesn't have to do with logic. Sometimes it just has to do with and I'm a hard-ass
Yeah, I am I went to good times the other day and then I guess he was wrapping up, but I would say many said
Leave him. Can I can I make a request of you? Leave him alone. Leave him alone right now because he's going through his own things.
not in a bad way, but he's doing a very good job
and you two need to be separate.
Okay.
Yeah, I wasn't pleasuring myself basically.
I was very in a speedo,
but I wasn't pleasuring myself.
Which isn't appropriate, but it was forced in July.
Don't do that anymore, please, Tim, please.
I won't, but-
Okay, so let's drop it.
We can drop it.
Let's just drop it.
just take, I can't force you to do anything, but take my advice on separate.
We had good conversations, that's a sad thing, but it's good.
But separate, you two are very different people, yet you are very similar.
And you are on the other side of his green screen.
Maybe I'm the green screen.
I am the green screen, even though I'm wearing coral today.
Have you ever seen my alien? I don't know if you've seen my alien.
I saw it, I saw it.
So I'm looking at my key, my key, the alien, the cat.
I've seen it many times.
OK.
I probably have an entire blueprint in my mind
of your place, whether you meant to show it or not.
Well, you have been outside.
Pretty much.
Yeah, so.
I know what your, I know what your place is.
I know what it looks like.
Yeah, you've been right to the front door.
I mean, yeah.
Remember we ran down the street and I was like gonna grab a couple beers.
Did you have fun or was it torture for you?
I had the best time, I had the best time, I really did.
I mean it's like I was absolutely everyone can tell I was like the picture I was like
this huge smile on my face and then I was you know streaming in between it and just.
You know, so excited talking in the chat and it was just, you're the first, first, the only first event ever.
I mean, I mean, well, I heard that you were going to be in another streamer.
Did that occur or it didn't happen?
So 300Glo was here, like he was in the area last night and he was going to come and he's like, I'm going to get me a pizza and I, what do you want to drink and stuff?
I think he's more fantasy than reality.
Yeah.
Because then, when it came down to it, he's like, I'm not coming.
So let's leave that on the shelf.
Okay.
So that-
He'll be the elf on the shelf for me.
Yeah, you don't want anything bad to happen.
Not to say that it would, okay, but-
Oh, I know.
I mean, to see, I talk a big game, but I'm actually in real life, I'm like, you know,
and-
I'm very respectful. I don't want to make people uncomfortable. I'm totally different. I mean, I'm the same as I am on
No, you're not
This is my personality, but it's like this personality is like
But maybe it's not a personality that you're ready to release into the world just yet, perhaps.
I'm not used to being extrovert. Like I said, I would have to get so drunk to start my show when I'm drunk.
And you don't want to have to do that in order to be that person.
You know, you got to find the equilibrium, the balance between, you know...
I feel that you have a lot of professionalism within you when you want to have it.
You definitely have a lot of intellect. You're naturally a showman. You are an actor.
You are. But you would probably be along the lines of myself as far as being more so of a method actor in a way.
But you have to have the right environment to have that.
and you have to, you know, it takes some things.
Yeah, I was actually, I mean, I was in some plays
when I was younger and I always wanted to be famous
or something, you know, but, you know,
I was also all very interested in Tarot when I was younger.
I was actually, there was a famous psychic named
Kenny Kingston.
I remember, yes.
Yeah, he had an infomercial he wrote a book about it's called, I still talk to and it's about he goes to the beach right here and he channels Lucille ball and different.
I mean, I read that book.
Really?
Yeah, and he had a hotline to it. I never called because you know, we had those numbers blocked in my house, but he was on K-Rock with like Dr. Drew and I guess it was.
Oh, I used to love Dr. Drew. Is he still doing his show?
I think.
Let me look it up. I used to really enjoy watching him.
That was like 12 13 it was like poor man and doctor that was before Ricky Rackman Ricky Rackman was the next after poor man
Poor man was like kind of like just yeah, he's still going. He's on YouTube
Yeah, doctor doing I liked him on the celebrity rehab show. I think he's a little bit, you know milk toast for me
But he's he's he's a showman. He's he's he's more of a
like a Reader's Digest version of psychology.
I've been to the Nerds, he was like that in college or something.
I don't know, but have you ever seen that movie?
I always thought he was more of a model turned psychologist.
He does like the face, he's like Zoolander.
He I mean he's not an unbad-looking guy. He's like he's attractive. He's a very nice looking man
He always gave me and he would always give great advice to people like they know
They have people call on about all kinds of things on that show and you know
We're really silly things sometimes like you you'd always take it very seriously
Which I liked and it's always good to have someone take you need everything seriously and that kind of thing
But yeah, I wish this was not every night. I was like 12. I had my radio and this is you know
I had my TV taken out of my room most of the time, so I would just have my
hay rock on and stuff. I'd like to stay up real late.
But there was one time, there was like, Kenny Kingston is going to be in the Canoga Park
Bowl. And I was like, oh my, in the second convention, I was so excited. I was 13 years old.
I was like, that's my brother who was like 10 years older than me.
And he's like, okay, we'll go to this, you know, the arena.
I mean, the bowl, you know, it's like, it's like, probably the Superbowl's there.
We drive out to Kanoga Park. It's the bowling alley.
It's the Kanoga Park bowling alley, the bowl.
Yeah, and so it's a little tiny bowling alley, and then it's like there's like, you know,
I've never been there, but I do know Kenoga Park.
I know the entire San Fernando Valley for the most part, because I lived in Hollywood.
I think what I remember going there really is for that, and actually, and I got a reading
from Kenny Kingston.
He actually said I'd be famous.
He said I'd be behind the camera and all kinds and in front of the camera, too.
And we talked personally, like after he did.
I mean, it's kind of weird because it kind of I did you're kind of doing it now
You just don't like the path that it's taking because it's very revealing to you
You want to reveal and dare I say and don't get offended when I say it, but it's truth
You want to exploit everybody else, but then when it comes to you?
I don't want to make people feel uncomfortable anything that they don't
I would like that at a time.
I always take boundaries.
I always take boundaries, but they have to be set, you know?
It's like they have to be set.
And then we're just like.
Well, you, you want, well.
I'm a little boundary dancer.
I like to move my mind and do like a little tight rope back.
Maybe that's the reason that you crossed my path.
Cause I, and I'm not being mean when I say, I broke you.
I broke you a little bit.
And you have to be, the way you are,
the way you're upbringing has been the way your mind works.
I think you might think that I'm more of a spoiled brat than I am because I'm actually
very I always was very like I love human beings I always kind of had like a and especially
now I'm kind of like a paternal attitude towards humanity like where it's like I don't really
hate okay well let's go with that let's say that you're paternal did I ever heard of you
Oh, no, I wouldn't be a mean dad, but at the same time I would be selfish. I'd be selfish. That's why I don't have you are you are naturally
You're you're you're a little mean. Well, not it. I mean if I don't have kids though
I mean, so it's like it doesn't matter you are mean
You know
I was just going I was to say my mom was like, oh you're so mean when I was little and now I look at her
I was like I was a fucking little brat and thank God you spanked me and you slap me like a few times because you know
You were trying to make us better people. I mean, it's like, you know
People don't appreciate moms enough.
I think sometimes because moms,
I mean, no matter what,
you know, women are,
you know, they like
they're having a nice flat
stomach and just imagine it's like all of a sudden
they have this huge, you know, it gets
stretched out and then like this watermelon comes out of the
lemon and stuff like that. And it's like, wow,
that's a sacrifice.
I mean, that's a huge, men wouldn't do it.
If men could get pregnant, they wouldn't.
Really, that's my opinion.
it still wouldn't be a thing.
And men are babies.
Someway, someway.
Someway, maybe you have like the Richard Simmons types.
I mean, some are like, you know, kind of like,
I don't know who would have a baby.
I mean, it's like, but, you know, I just appreciate it.
I mean, but I also, you know, it's like, you know,
I appreciate, you know, parents that are.
are there and it's like, because it's like, you know,
it takes a village, I guess,
like Hillary Clinton used to say,
I don't know if you, you don't like that,
but that's the one thing I did like to say.
I'm not against that saying, it does.
It takes, well, not just when someone's a child,
but when you become an adult too,
that's why you have your social circle.
Yeah.
But you have to be, you have to use discernment.
Right.
And not just by default out like I understand that you want to be a modern-day hippie good for you
Hey, not me
Charles Manson sure if you I think you need to use discernment you got to let people earn
your trust
And you have to realize that you have to earn other people's trust, and when certain boundaries are breached,
sometimes you can't earn that trust back. Sometimes you can. You have to let time go by, experience, it can't always be instant gratification.
it takes time and sometimes things are tested but sometimes it just depends
person to person to person sure and you can't you know stereotype or rule
certain things in or out as a default and sometimes you have to accept heart
You know, what you think is heartbreak is actually a level of development, right? There's a lot of factors
We can't control any other people right and it's like and so that's like a hard thing because we
That's like it's like hard to be able to billion other people or billions of people to deal with and everyone's kind of different in their own way
It gets complicated the more so it's like, you know, I can only take
Kind of so much people like people. I'm you know, I'm not very social like I'm very shy in public that kind of thing
I can't really but
I'm friendly enough, but it's just I'm just I'm just shy. It's like without you two or like this. I would not
Really have a social life. I don't think right now. You need more
And this is just my opinion
At some point there does have to be at least two
crossovers that you have from your online life to your offline life to
assimilate you. I mean look we all went through the COVID thing and that set
everybody back especially if you're an introvert to an extent okay but with
you I feel that you're gonna have to have because for you to be comfortable and
who knows you know
I'm going to pray for this for you.
I hope that God sends somebody into your life
who can be your offline.
social life to assimilate you more because you would do very well in the
offline life. You know you have openers, you're funny, you look nice. I've got you
the business card so you have an opener with that. Yeah. But you know there does
need to be more of a bridge because you cannot only be indoors. You can't be a
It's not healthy for you, and I'm not saying you have to be outside all the time, but a little bit more than you are right now
I think this city is very
It's very you know, I know LA is it's
In the three there's one gay bar. I guess in the three city area here
It's not in the cities like another city over and so I've never even been there
There's I've been to the sports for maybe once to come too expensive
I'm not like you know I'm not very good with like I mean it's kind of expensive to go out
and stuff. You need something that's going to be a set scheduled outside of the house
activity but to where it's safe and comfortable for you. I've thought about this when it comes to
I have traveled a lot. I had opportunity when I was like 14, 15, I went to like Spain, Greece, and then I was 17, I went to Thailand, and then I went to Europe when I was like 19, and I went to a bunch of countries there.
I've also been to China, and Mexico, and Canada. So I have gotten to like actually like travel a little bit, and then we've looked, you know.
We have this we have this we've traveled stuff in our charts. I anyway, but uh, and so I got a chance to do that
I would love to do that still it's not as easy and
Yeah, um, but
would love to I mean there's a lot of families here and stuff like that and
it's like just even with my family everyone has everyone has their own
families now it's like kind of like it's very different and so we're older now
yeah and you know I and I don't have that and it's my fault right but at the
same time I'm still in my mind I'm a handful to take care of myself and so
Did it ever occur to you that you're designed to maybe take care of people that are not related to you
But who are in a similar boat to you? It took me a while to come to that conclusion
I would love to like, you know
Life sometimes just takes me to these certain places and it's like and then you say oh that was the reason this happened
This was this is why and it's like all the path because everything that's happened to us
That makes us who we are like if we don't have that experience that we would be a different person to pretty much
So it's like we're very
product of our of our past in a certain way we also have an option to change it and to you know to look but
We're always finding ourselves at this present moment. This is our it's hard to like what do we do right now?
But like right now it's like you have to have that focus and then
I have been able to use, I love the website I made,
I still love it, I love the show I've done.
I think I've done, I mean, this show has been
I mean, thousands and thousands of hours.
I mean, it's like, I mean, I've talked to so many people.
You've got up here production quality,
and I've tried to work with you on that,
and you're not, you're not.
doing my suggestions for my frustration is.
Right. I understand. I understand. I mean, I try not to like lay down under the blanket. I have
done that a few times. I try to like have my green screen up, but sometimes it's hard to see cars and
stuff. And I mean...
I'm but here here's a hard to see cars cars cars when I oh cars cars
Okay, the good thing is I did a really good cleaning and that's like well you I heard you say that you
Rearrange your furniture, so you did like a little thing Shway or something. This is like Lola right here
She's obviously I had the I had this word this by the window right there. Okay
All right, so you've rearranged just so that everyone knows this place is kind of like a loft in a way like, you know
He's it's like upstairs and you know, but um
Alex never said the codex is trash Alex always was very well
She knows she was a little suspicious of the codex at first, but she was very complimentary when she looked at it
And you know, and I I'm really happy to like
I want you're gonna have to do more manual stuff with it and stop relying so much on the AI.
Well, yeah, I mean, but there I mean, I know you mean because it's like every time a new episode
comes in, it like puts the name sometimes different. And so it creates all these different names that
I'm not going to criticize the codex today. I'll make another. Actually, I need to make notes
as far as what I need to make notes to send you because otherwise I'll forget.
I just wanna, is Nick Johnson in the chat because, you know,
I don't know about Alex, but I can use a lab dance right now.
Nick Johnson.
I'm just kidding, okay, it's a joke, it's a joke.
All right, so, I didn't even hear you just now,
so I'm not that bad.
Okay, okay, ignore me, ignore me, I'm just being stupid.
Okay, Nick, if I'm as gay now,
I need to send you a detailed account
about exactly what I'm upset about.
Okay.
and I need to send you my thoughts as of current on the codex
because I do have additional thoughts.
Because I can implement those, you know, and I will, because I do take your...
Well, you do, you do.
And, you know, it is a very, it's a huge, huge project.
I mean, it has over, like, half a million transcript statements.
And so it's like, there's, I mean, it would take 100 years to do it manually, right?
And so just, it's a, I mean, I'm doing it to be able to do something.
No, there's some sub-routines that you could use to fix a few things.
Thank you. I mean, I'd appreciate, because I know something, you know something.
I mean, it's like, it's really, it's really.
Well, I went to school for computer science. I told you that, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
And, I mean, I've always, my dad never used a computer.
Until he passed away, he had like a little ledger.
He had like a handwritten ledger that he'd do all his business
on, he'd do the math on that and everything.
But he always wanted me to have a computer.
And, so I was like 13, 14, either 46 or whatever.
And had this computer, I had Carmen San Diego
and what I mean, I don't know, Oregon Trail or something.
and then the internet came and then the internet came I got in kind of a little trouble because
maybe the internet wasn't a little bit too uh too fast for me for that age you know because I was
just gonna get faster yeah that's when I was kind of interested in like you know I was like you know
I was friends with like a lot of older people like you know in high like they were in high school
I was like an eighth grade and stuff in eighth grade and so I was like a virgin and then it's like
it made fun of me kind of and so I was like I was like I gotta lose my virginity so I'd go on these
there were just chat rooms, like there wasn't even like really pictures that I mean you could get like
one rainy photo or something really that was the thing to lose your virginity really well I mean
I wanted I was very much pent up in my house and like not allowed to juice up so I would like I would
like you know sneak out right see people and I was bad I was a bad bad teenager and it's like you
know I I had my door taken off at one point you know they just my parents took the door off the
you know so I can have some privacy but I would see people I was bad I was a bad little brat and
it's like man it's like but wow I mean it's like
I, I, I don't know. I was, I, I don't know if being gay, I, I got away with things more.
I am gay and I, I am, and it's like, I mean, it's interesting. I didn't date that woman and stuff.
As for attraction, I'm, I'm very attracted to men.
Um, I feel like we should talk about that later.
Okay, let's do that later.
I'm not right now.
Okay.
And I'm not going to attack your chat.
It's your chat.
It's your show.
I feel exactly my chat.
It's not going to be all that.
Fuck my chat.
There are certain people in the chat that need a word.
And I feel like I'm not going to address it on your show.
I'm just going to do my thing over on my channel.
Unrelated to you.
They're not going to know why it's happening.
I tend to be like that.
I'll come out of nowhere.
But, um, there's gonna be some things that happen after I've read a few things that were in your chat from some people who think that I didn't see it.
I'm not mad, I just will address it.
I'm a 47-year-old bitch, truthfully.
And it's never going to change.
You know what, that's the thing, it's like we can accept each other for who we are.
That's a beautiful thing.
I mean, it's like, you know, and it's like, hey, I'm a huge, I mean, I'm a huge bitch.
You know, I'm a huge bitch.
I'm excited to see where you're going to be exactly.
Let's see, where are we in July right now?
almost in August. I'm excited where you're going to be August of 2028. You'll be happy
with it, in my opinion. I think you'll be happy. But you're going to grow a lot if you let yourself,
you've got to stop thinking that you're not accepted.
You are and that's what that's what bothers me the most about you. Honestly, you sit in there being like
Nuts me everybody hates me people don't hate you
They don't, you know, I mean, you're in a certain community.
So by default, you're gonna, you know,
it's gonna be what it is.
You chose to be here.
Yeah.
Okay.
You've been granted admittance.
Right.
Do you understand how many people in these communities
actually do really like you a lot?
And the fights are what helped people get to know you.
Do you understand that people dislike me more than they dislike you?
They hate that we're talking right now yet. They love it
They love it yet. They hate it that let them hate me because I can take it
But the more that they hate me the better
Okay, they there's someone in this chat right now. I'm not even and I've ignored him the entire time
And do you know how much he hates it due to his level of vanity because he used to be the superstar
He's a superstar no mole and he knows it and he hates it
And that's why he's always trying to get my attention because I am the one who good does get to kind of
Crown the superstars whether people know it or not and he never gets the crown again
And I'm doing it out of spite because I think he has a bad attitude and I have the power I've got the power and I do so too bad so sad and I mean who am I talking about you'd have to know to know I know you know but yeah he's mad about that and it's fitting punishment for him considering a few things and considering he's more and grateful
Honestly, it's very similar to you too, even though you will never admit it, but I've
teased the bathroom.
Do you mind if I take a break?
Go ahead.
Absolutely.
All right.
Give me like 10 to 15 minutes.
Maybe somebody else wants to come up.
Who knows?
I'll put the link.
If anyone wants to come up.
Yeah.
Thank you, Alex.
What would I have?
Let me see.
Yeah.
You know, you know, there's certain comedians Jim Carrey, I guess was one and like Robin Williams
No, they're very funny people, right?
They you know millions of people just like you know laugh and they you know the other movies and stuff
But it's like you look and they they kind of had a little bit of a sadder
family life
Oprah too. Yeah, and uh, you know
That's why they're so funny sometimes is because the humor can be a defense mechanism and it can be like a way to lighten the
Detention there's sometimes there's a lot of fighting and it's like, you know, and then if they there's that one kid that can just like
Do make a joke and everyone's laughing instead of screaming at each other. I mean, that's that's a good thing, you know
Here I'll play this I'll play this video. This is a word of deed of on teeth anybody. I haven't heard this
I just saw the video. It looks interesting. So I'm gonna play this deed of on teeth video
Oh my god, Shriners are involved in something. Okay, hold on a second. Here we go
I'm going to share this video and this is called Black Widow, Edita Von Teese and Monarchy, okay?
Kind of like more like, um, let's try this one. This is one of my favorite. I never heard that one
before but this one is one of my favorites. I don't know if you've seen this but this is so good.
It's called Disintegration. This you will love. This is the hit right here.
When there is just one woman left standing in your room then she will be yours.
Now, the first mosquito, not gita, your arty, the mosquito, am I the only one to help buy
over the mosquito?
I have one more, let me see, this is scissors sisters, scissors sisters, this is one of
my favorite videos, it's very cultish though, it's called invisible light, and I hope you
enjoy.
Oh my god, okay pause, okay, read your guys, enjoy.
I'm gonna stick go hey takes one I know one Gotti here we go
That's one of the more artistic ones, but yeah, yeah, I'm putting something backstage as soon as I do
Chronicles 29. No, no, no look at the private chat. Okay. Okay
Okay, just
Okay, gotcha. Just and I'm gonna tell you why backstage. I'm gonna tell you why okay. It's selfish reasons
Hold on. How are you enjoying Chronicles and then we'll listen to the song because the song that I it was the song
I was telling you about the little AI diddy that I did
Yeah, okay. Do you see what I just wrote? Okay?
Yes
Okay
Okay. Yeah, you got it. That's thank you
Deleted it or you can I don't care what you do with it, but I'm just telling you because
Just for everyone to be
Yeah for a bit it'll be okay
Cool. Gamble says he wants his crown back. He was catching straights. Why am I catching straights?
I have nothing. I've said so many positive things about him in the past. I've said some negative things about him as of recent.
I have nothing else to say about him now. And I think that, you know, the way I look at these communities is maybe
Maybe because I was raised in like a corporate environment in a way, that's how I view things in a certain capacity.
You know, this, let's say that this is Microsoft, okay, then you got Logitech.
You got, I don't know, Alienware or Gateway, you know, whatever the popular computer companies
are right now.
And everyone does kind of intertwine and work together, but at the same time there's competitors.
And that's all that there is to it.
Sometimes we do, sometimes we don't.
And I don't have a fight with Gamble.
I don't really have a fight with anybody.
I stay on my ground and I think that people
are not used to that, you know, but I do.
But I really don't antagonize.
I tend to, as you've said, you respond.
I tend to respond also.
But I think sometimes my response is
because they're so potent.
are misconstrued as antagonizing,
but I'm just saying that I shut things down quick,
swiftly, that's how I was taught.
And I do that in every aspect of my life,
and some people don't like it.
I mean, I have a hard time with romantic relationships
because I'm a certain way, but I accept myself.
It is what it is.
But yeah, so I have another Christian-inspired song.
from the book of Chronicles, that's where I am right now,
my Bible reading, if you don't want to hear it,
you don't have to.
I do, so is that one you have posted right now, backstage?
Yeah.
Okay, okay, here you go, here you go.
Chronicles 29, everybody.
David said to all the assembly, Solomon my son,
the one whom God has chosen is young and inexperienced.
And the work is great since the palace is not for a man,
but for the Lord God.
So with all my might, I have prepared for the house of my God
3000 Talonar and 7000 talents of refined silver
Self today then the leaders of the father's houses
The leaders of the tribes of Israel
Captains of thousands and hundreds and the officials of the King's workers offered willingly
They donated to the service of the house of God
Gave them to the treasury of the house of the Lord custody of jail. It's like, you know some parts of the Bible are a little bit dry
You know, but I mean it's exciting
I mean, it's a time on towns that Silver's and Golden they well it talks about what we were talking about earlier when it comes to
you know that dichotomy of
People who are so entrenched
upon being religious, upon, you know, wanting to do things by the book when it
comes to whatever their level or whatever their faith is, but it taking
people with money who have been in the world to be able to fund it, you know?
And that's the disconnect, but it happens. And I mean, when you really read the Bible,
what a lot of the disputes were about.
And you see it is still today.
You have people who are like,
oh, you're not of the Lord, you're not of the Bible,
you're not of God, you're not of Jesus Christ.
Look at you, look at all the immoral things that you've done.
And it's like, yeah, but I'm also creating your church.
And I'm funding things and without someone who's actually been in the world
You're not going to be able to achieve what you want to
Necessarily achieve when it comes to spreading the word of whatever your faith is. It's so
Theory the woman at the well. I think was the woman at the Wells Fargo. Yeah
And uh, maybe I think she was a banker and that's why you know, you kind of knew her.
I think Mary Magdalene was a business woman. I don't care what anybody says about that.
She's my relative. They are. I think that I strongly believe that there have been a lot of
women throughout the Bible. That's why when people want to call me a horror, they insult me. I really
don't take it as an insult, especially as I've been doing my Bible reading because I look at the
Okay, she was a business woman and I'm not saying that she was always, you know, I don't
agree with a lot of things that I've read about her, but at the same time.
she did, she was a notable character or person figure in the Bible and there's a
reason that we know about her and you know there's a lot of controversial
figures in the Bible but without those controversial figures would you have
the greatness and the glory? Probably not.
Right. I know, like, you know, there's a book of Judith in the Bible, and Judith, like, actually,
like, she was kind of a spy, and, like, you know, I think she, like, killed some kind of giant guy
with the hammer or something like that in the middle of the night. Like, I mean, so it's like,
there are really, like, spicy, like, true crime stories in the Bible.
Well, I mean, I mean, I was talking about, um...
You know what I've been talking about lately when it's come to you. What's that? What's that Damon's name again?
Sarah yeah, I hate to say it, but
That's that's why I'm gonna I'm gonna continue to be hard on you about that. Yeah, the story of Sarah does parallel
tremendously
Beta
Okay, well, I was may I say one thing because I didn't do a little research because I I did say an osmotic
It's a little bit before but I did I did research and refresh because it's the book of Tobit in the Bible
And there's Sarah's Mary to it. Hope it is not in every Bible. That's yeah specialized book. Yeah
Yeah, it's especially it's like the apocryphae or something like that or like yes, and uh, but what happens is it's like Tobit
Or Sarah, actually, she has like seven
fiancees and they all died before the wedding day.
Like, and so she's like, I'm cursed or something is wrong.
So what I.
I mean, I read a lot of different perspectives of it.
One thing I said was that Asmoni is actually in love with her
and he wanted it to be with her.
Well, let's define love, love.
Married because he's gonna be in the world.
He couldn't be in the world unless he found a wife.
So, you know, if you can't be in a person's world.
He couldn't be married her.
If you can't be in a person's,
I mean, it's like the freaking little mermaid, you know.
I want to be a part of your world.
Well, maybe you can't be a part of everybody's world all the time.
And even if you want to be part of the world.
So why didn't he let her go?
I mean, seven deceased.
And it's like, I mean, if you're a man and then it's like,
and you're like considering what I put backstage.
OK, yeah.
OK.
And that's why I'm saying, and I'm not
saying that you are that demon.
I think that you didn't poke it a little bit,
but you could just agree with me on that.
But I'll say let it let it be because the reason that I have been very curious about
The thing that is and whatnot. I want I want a certain person to have a chance
breathe. I would love I would love I even if I'm not invited I would love to
just have and see how things progress and maybe it won't even be him maybe it'll
be but she but what I heard in her voice on a thing I did a tiny and little
commentary on earlier today I heard a lot of pain
Right, I mean, I know that and that broke my it broke me to an extent hearing that pain because I'm not her friend
I don't talk to her behind the scenes. I don't know certain realities versus
Lies that were told to me and I don't even want to know but what I heard
it hurt
a part of me because I felt like that before.
Yeah.
And I want her to be able to breathe.
So I mean, I basically had to threaten somebody recently
to call off their enforcers.
But considering that you and I have a good rapport,
what I am gonna say is, let her go for a little bit.
Just just oh, yeah, I mean I will and it's like because I mean it's please please for me for me just for me
I'm basically I'm not gonna go anywhere where I'm not one like in the future. It's not about that. It's about a woman
needing space and to be a woman like it's even if you have a lot of feminine energy in you as a man or a male
as a woman, it's such a different story.
And I can't even imagine it because I'm not a woman
and I know women feel for it.
I couldn't imagine being a man.
I mean, that's rough in itself.
Right.
And, but, just.
I understand.
And you'll be happy how it ends up.
I promise you, I promise you.
You can kick my ass if I'm wrong, but I know I'm right.
I know I'm right and you know, sometimes I will bet you I will just if I'm I'm not going to say that what I'm going to say is that she will reconnect to you before you think to reconnect with her platonically.
So just give it, because I know that you're, see, you're a little impatient.
I can be impatient too, definitely, but I've just waited so long for things on an occasion
that I've lost my impatience because I know how long things can take.
But in that particular situation or this particular situation that we're talking of that I don't
It's not going to take as long as you think, but you just being a little stronger than you normally would be.
I'm going to slow my roll.
All the difference in the world.
I'll slow my roll.
And I will keep you company.
I'll make the effort, because it does mean something to me, because I want to see if I'm wrong, really.
Hey, I think, you know, women are usually proven right.
I mean, it's like, you know, there's something
in the intuition that understands the complexity
is a little bit better than men's.
She's a little bit older than I am,
but she's walked a, not a similar path to me,
but she's a certain kind of woman that I tend to be.
And, you know, give it a shot.
I like it, I like it, yeah.
I mean, it's like, I wanna really like focus
on my own show and you know.
And that's not the only reason I came on here
just so that you're aware.
It's not on behalf of anybody.
I'm just, it crossed my mind
when I was having a cigarette outside
and I was like, you know what?
I need to talk to him about that.
So I did.
Good, cause I wanna, I mean, I really like,
I am like a very, I'm a libertarian more politically.
I'm just very like, I want people to be free, happy.
and pursuit of the American dream and all that kind of stuff, right?
And, you know, and I don't want to interfere.
I want to, I'm basically, you know, gay people actually are like kind of behind the scenes in a lot of the straight world.
Like, or it's like, you know, wedding planners.
Probably not as much as you think.
Yeah, but I'm thinking like I'm making artists, hairdressers.
I mean, think about like all the wedding planners of a wedding.
I mean, this is like gay men who brought, I mean, now they will have a wedding.
Maybe they need to say an age because it's more acceptable.
I'm not, I'm not, I don't think I'm a mod in your chat anymore.
But I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to do a power move if you do.
I'm in here as IRL Neustime.
Let me put it like a little.
I'm just going to type hi so you can do it, so you can see my thing.
I'm going to do a power move because I'm real sick of him at this point.
I'm real sick of him.
OK, you got to do what you got to do, one second.
I just, and I'm probably bringing in some hate upon myself,
upon me doing what I need to do.
But I feel like he has his own platforms.
He's been around for a long time.
There's absolutely zero reason for him to be doing what he's doing.
And if I could and get away with it legally,
I would put my foot down his throat at this stage.
Yeah.
All right, I did it.
I did it.
And I won't do it to anybody else, but I had enough.
I'm sorry.
To the person that I did that to, you take it out on me
so I can do what,
you need to be glad that I'm a woman because if I was a man it would be a
whole different ball game. I would probably be in prison really when I think about it.
I mean I have heard that the theory that women do not have to clean up blood
for girls. I don't know about that. I'm not gonna do anything to anybody else.
Okay, well nobody else nobody else not not at the moment. There is somebody who just entered the chat who uh
Yeah, but I'm not gonna do it to him or anything because I think with him
I could do it in person, but we're not gonna go there right now. Let me shut up
Maybe I'll wolf out
Was there a Teen Wolf and there was a Teen Wolf with the woman?
I don't know if there was.
I always figured I would be more of a cat woman, really.
What if, you know, the wolf and the cat, I mean, that'd be very strange, I guess.
A bat and a cat, I mean, Batman and Cat would match up.
I mean, they fought a little bit, but they were, they were.
Well, there's Spider-Man and then, well, like, what superheroes are there?
The Hulk.
Animal, the Hulk, yeah.
Is that Robert Downey Jr. play?
Hey, man, she-ra, well, that's a different series.
There's, oh, how about Gem in the hologram?
Oh, that was my gem, gem, gem.
Truly brave as you, gem.
Yeah, the music's contagious.
Oh, look, he's trying to come back.
Look at that.
No.
No, look, I mean, he's supposed to be such a big deal
and so smart and fabulous.
Shouldn't his own platform?
Why is he here?
I have some ults that I go and chat
that I'm not welcome in, and I'll go in.
Wow.
Well, that's what I was saying.
You think that you're not accepted.
You're kind of, you know, you're
King of the Castle, and I'm just kind of a,
and you have the rule, I'm just being bad.
Hey, my mods, my mods can run free basically,
because you know, I can't,
it's kind of like hard for me to moderate the chat sometimes.
I mean, I like, it's just like,
my mouse is not even working very well right now,
so I'm kind of-
And I might, someone's asking,
why are you not even controlling?
Cause I had, he was, he gave me a little bit of power.
be careful who you get power to.
I'm not doing it to anyone else, just one person.
If friends have a car, two friends have a car
and then it's like sometimes one of them will wanna drive
and the other person will say, okay,
I'm gonna lay down and maybe I'll fall asleep.
I hopefully won't and then I'm sorry
if I did on Hollywood because-
Really clumsy after you brought up something
about my father when you don't want things
brought up about your family, really, really clumsy.
Really, after I've already forgiven you,
whereas I shouldn't have,
whereas I already shielded you,
you're gonna really challenge me.
You think that you're something, you're nothing.
Nothing.
And you remember that, little boy.
Do you really wanna fight me, clumsy?
I don't think you do.
Tell me.
Do you really want to?
Cause you're not strong enough.
Do you really want to, clumsy?
Do you want to fight me?
Do you wanna fight me?
don't think you do. Stand down right now. Know your place. No, I don't care about
your mother. Your mother will be ashamed of you right now. Do you want to fight
me clumsy? Answer the question yes or no, because I will make sure that you not
only don't have a platform, I will make sure that you suffer other
consequences that you cannot even imagine. Do you want to do that clumsy? Think
I have been so kind to you. So gracious. Do you want to do it? Already you have more enemies
than you even know. Do you want to do it? I'm not being dramatic. I'm asking you a question.
Do you want to do it? Yes, it's a threat, boy. Do you want to do it? You have five seconds to
You've answered the question yeah, I mean you're an idiot, but I'm not surprised
So clumsy is not gonna have a YouTube channel soon
too bad so sad
Well, I see, like, oh, there's, I mean, there's like a lot of people, there's a lot of, there's, I think it's the Chris Lanz here. Is that Katrina?
I don't have any issue with anyone else in your chat, but clumsy overcepts his bounds. He's a user, and already good times has an issue with clumsy, and I tried to smooth that over. Now I understand why.
And I promote it clumsy. You know, clumsy wouldn't have as popular of a channel if it worked for me, or good times.
and he doesn't understand who made him.
I mean, I do know a lot of people that were helpful
and it's like that he kind of turned on and it's like.
You know, I'm not certain that he told the truth about the beta situation
Messages and I just wasn't impressed like sometimes one school day
Oh, I prove us something and then I say here
I'm like, I don't understand the context or what's really going on about it
And so it's like well
There's a piece of video that he would definitely rather not be out there and I know who has it
I mean, I don't really understand why he says that he's a predator hunter when he took money
from a group of alleged predators recently, and then he doesn't want certain things out
about himself.
And then there's so many things from the past that people have forgotten about that could
easily be released, and I've been nothing but kind to him, as has others who are people
I guess he thinks that he's bigger than he is.
Hmm.
Um, gentlemen, I do like clowns.
I've actually related to the first clown, Joseph Ramaldi.
Oh, don't worry, Clumsy. You're gonna get a whole fucking website.
It's not gonna be a YouTube battle.
And we do know who you live with.
Just saying.
And it won't be me. It'll be somebody else.
Oh, my gosh. Nick Johnson's in the chat.
He's just flirty. I want to do a flirty diamond video,
but I don't have the balls, he says.
Come on girl girl pair. I mean come on
See what you don't understand clumsy is that sometimes it's not about getting the clips. It's about already having them
You're not sophisticated enough for this game. You're also not smart enough. I never liked you. I just tolerated you
Don't forget that clumsy
Anthony
Like, uh, well, you know, it was interesting seeing like I don't know if she's like Chris K was on the other night
And he had I think that this Hispanic woman that was next door and she she was in the department like dancing
I thought that might have been INX to you
You know? Was I the only one who thought that? No way. I couldn't have been
What yeah, I mean it's like I mean that that lady was interesting, but and then it's Lori
She was interesting, wasn't she?
Yeah, she didn't like the camera on her very much,
but she was feeling free.
And then Flirty had a...
She's in this I guess her sugar daddy a call or something like that, but she's she's all over spitting this guy's mouth on every channel
What is going on flirt? Oh, was she really? I thought she was just hanging out. I didn't see I haven't watched
Yeah, well, she's like
And he's like like so skinny on the porch like he looks like I thought it was like a corpse
I thought she'd killed him, but it was he was alive
But he was just like like suddenly a tanning or something like that and then she's like leans down
I hate when people, I think it's gross, I can't, I'm not, I'm not about the, like, that kind of thing, it grosses me out, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Anthony, nobody cares what you post because you don't matter.
Do you understand how insignificant you are?
And because of your criminal history,
do you understand that nobody will ever believe a word
that you say?
It doesn't matter what you do.
What you're doing when it comes to me
is coming up against an entity that you can never dominate.
And truthfully, I don't understand
why you're with a woman, honestly.
And I'm not saying that in the worst of ways, I'm just saying it as many in these communities
think of you.
I thought the picture of the red ball in his mouth was real.
Did you see that picture of the red ball?
I think that he was just pulling a ball.
Well, I think it might be, really.
I don't want to fight with him.
I just don't like that he's challenging me.
He's doing it because he feels that somehow it's going to elevate him and that I'm going
to back down.
Absolutely not.
No. Because I've never liked you. I've tolerated you, Anthony, because of good times who will always be a very good friend of mine.
And the only reason that you were privy to being friends with him was simply because of me.
There's a lot of things that happen in these communities specifically because of me. I normally don't brag about it.
It's not a vain thing. It's not me being a narcissist. None of it. It's just the facts.
the center that you realize that the better off you will be. I think you need
to just chill, Anthony. If you can't, hey, you can't. You never could. That's why
you did extensive prison time. That is why you are shameful to your children.
There's a lot of things about you that you would probably rather the public not discuss
And I'm being very careful about what I say because truth be told this would not be a fight that ends online
This would be something that is dealt with offline. You are dealing with something that you don't quite know
Just saying and I'm intoxicated saying this to you, but I'm saying it a very kind nice way
I think so so I'm gonna drop it
I'm gonna ignore you from this point on because I'm having a really good night tonight and you're ruining it because well
You're a loser. Why would you come in here and ruin?
a good night for other people.
Why? Because you don't have any traffic.
Why don't you go start your own stream right now?
That's what you tend to do.
You've done it with good times,
and good times has been so gracious and kind to you,
forgiving of you.
But you really did hurt his feelings recently,
and I did not like that.
And I'm not the only one who didn't like that.
There's a few of us women who don't like that.
So you're not just contending with me. You're contending with some other women who choose not to speak. I'm speaking for them
Know your place Climsy and your place ain't here. It ain't here
It ain't here. It's not even on the screen. It's somewhere down there. I hope you understand
Really? He turned on me too. I mean it's like that's crazy. I mean it's like
And I'm sorry that I just disrespected your podcast.
No, you're fine.
You're fine.
Because you're really apologize.
You're a mod and I want you to feel comfortable here and I don't mind.
Take away my mod.
I should not mod anybody else.
I'm done modding.
No more modding.
It was just, I thought it was one.
It turned out to be two.
I'm surprised it was two.
But then again, I'm not surprised considering who he took money from recently, meaning number
two.
You know if you need the money take the money, but don't think that people don't know
We all know it's this very small close knit community. We all know and in the end we all do work together
We're all entertainers
if we're legitimate entertainers we are and
And being entertainers not always easy to say because it's like I mean really especially like you know like
We're giving a lot and and everything and it's like it's like
I mean, so so many people are so sour about things and and oh, you know, and then they're putting oh, no
I don't want to hear your new music. I mean to me and stuff like that
I mean, it's like it's like hey, don't go to another show like I'm here to like share myself
It's not just like I'm not I have my show so people I mean
I want people to chat and I have a good time, but don't forget like it's like
About pity things really
We fight about such piddly, stupid, stupid things.
And I do want to make it known that what I just said, that was me.
That did not have anything to do with psych.
It had nothing to do with anyone else, but it did have to do with good times
because good times is somebody I care about.
and we'll always fight about certain things,
but it's just been so much time that has gone by,
and he knows me so well, and I know him so well,
that I'm not okay with certain people
hurting his feelings, because he doesn't say anything.
And I kind of, I view myself as like,
a big sister to certain people, even if they hate me, I don't care.
We do have a guest on and I think you've met this person in real life.
Oh, who?
Hey!
Hey.
How are you doing?
Good, it's my birthday.
Well, wait, wait, wait, let me get another drink.
Wait a minute, I got a break out.
I got a little bit of, I got a little tequila.
I got a tiny bottle.
Oh, hell yeah, hell yeah.
Will you hold on?
Will you hold on one second?
For sure.
Give me just, I'm gonna use the restroom.
I'm gonna, I gotta prepare.
Everybody, LD, LD, tell them a happy,
I didn't even know it was your birthday.
I don't know any of your birthday.
Yeah, yeah, thank you.
It's so good to see you.
Good to see you too, I hope.
Just give me five minutes, please.
Give me five minutes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't go anywhere, don't go anywhere.
No, of course not.
ALD, how are you doing tonight?
Good, long time no see, man.
How you been?
Yeah, it has been.
I want to do a little, like, I don't know if I've
ever done this for you before, but there's
a book that has all the birthdays in it.
And I'm looking for a book.
Oh, shit.
727?
728.
728 so you're a
Okay, you're okay
So this is from a secret language of birthdays, and this is like I try to do this for people especially when it's a birthday
Let me see if I can find it. Okay got it July 27th perfect. Okay. No 28 28. Oh my gosh
It's the next tomorrow. It's tomorrow. Yeah, it's not my birthday technically in California yet. I got I got you
So I'm gonna just change for July. Yeah, okay. God
Perfect. Okay. Go back one. Okay. So, July 28th is called the, um, okay. July 28th, I'm opening it. Okay. So this should be, okay. July 28th, the day of the winner. Okay.
It's called the day of the winners is positive, resourceful, and dynamic.
Those born on July 28th often manifest a strong desire to be first in their social or occupational
sphere.
Their form of authority is literally embodied in their person.
More important than that than what they say or think is with who they are.
That those who come in contact with even the mildest of persons born this day will soon learn that occupying a secondary position
Is not what a july 28th person has in mind
Those born in this day are real survivors who are not content to just weather the storm
But to come out on top in every realm of life from the game room to the bedroom to the
Interstangdom of the corporate boardroom. So those born on this day
those born in this day seek to prevail. Of course, such driven personality states great emotional
challenges. Others may find them unresponsive or accuse them of being insensitive when they go for
their objective. This is awesome. This is awesome. Okay. So he's reading my horoscope for my actual
Yeah, I don't know if you could repeat it. Alex is really, Alex has known me a long time, I think it sounds too fucking accurate to me.
Accurate, yeah.
I didn't even know you were Leo, I didn't know what you're saying.
You know my last name, you know my last name of course.
Yeah, but I'm not going to look up your, okay, I get it, okay, it took me a second.
I'm a Leo, you know what my last name is and I'm allergic to cats.
Wow, that's funny, that's funny.
How have you been?
You look good, you look great.
Good, I bought a house.
Oh, congratulations, yay.
It's very nice, very nice.
Very good. Amazing. Yes. For you. Good for you. It's been about two months now.
It's a nice little place. And you look really good.
Like, I mean, it's like, yeah, I've seen you like not as healthy looking.
I mean, you look really great. You look super handsome.
You look healthy. You look happy. Nice, yeah.
You look great. You look great. You look great.
Yeah, you look great.
I took my sister and my mom and my niece out this weekend because I was off.
So we all met up for my birthday.
We went to the zoo and had a really good time.
We had like a lunch and it was really nice, you know, I enjoyed myself.
So yeah, it was good seeing everybody.
Good for those who don't know
LD and I initially met what we're at Fremont Street
Everyone's hanging out on Fremont Street when I had the big fucking beard. I looked like a fucking hole
Well, you I have a nice face so you don't have to worry about you know trying to cheat a chin or anything like that
But um, yeah
We have fun. We have pizza. We have beer. We hung out. We have such a good time. We had a joint. We had such a good time
We had such a good time. It was so short. I think it was only one day. Yeah, it was it was one day
But this man he is the ultimate person to hang out with perfect gentlemen. So now there we go. There we go
There she is
Yeah, I was it looks disgusting. It looks
It's dark. I mean, it's like well, he has dark hair. He has dark hair
Mine is like my beard like come look at my beard all gray now. I mean, it's like I look at the mirrors
I was like, oh, LD is younger than you
I'm 62 years old
33 like 34 35 I'm 62 bro. I was born when Lyndon B. Johnson was present
He has an old soul.
LD is super young, actually.
He's young.
He just acts because he's had to have a lot of responsibilities.
LD has been through stuff.
Remember, well, I know about the motorcycle accident.
He was basically.
I'm not gonna say everything, but LD has been hell and back a few times. Okay, but he is a
Wonderful person. He has that wonderful spirit about him
I'm not gonna say what you do for a living
But he is somebody who cares about people helps people constantly
always has been somebody in the public service and
He's a badass
LD is the guy that you want to know
Yeah, like yeah, he will like if there's an emergency he will save your fucking life
Okay, that's him
Is the same way interestingly enough they're almost like twins even though there's an age difference who?
You're you're sibling. I'm not gonna. I don't want yeah, I mean like listen. I love my sister. I absolutely fucking love her
I think I think I think my sister
you chased her and
Basically saved your life. I don't care anyone says about I thought I wasn't gonna let that should happen and listen
I'm not I'm not here to talk about any of that stuff. Cheers everybody. We all gotta do cheers. Cheers everybody
Many many many more years for you. Thank you. Thank you. All right
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I used to get so drunk at the holiday parties at our office because I would order the alcohol and then I'd like, you know, I'd just order all.
Yeah, I mean, you were like with some, like, onka before LD or some skonka that I threw
with something at you, you know, it's like, she threw something at your head or something,
you had a band on your head, you were in bad shape, and I was worried about you, you had
a woman throwing things at you, because you were-
What are you talking about?
Yeah, what are you talking about?
He was like, he had a band in on his head, and he said, oh, I had, I was fucking this
girl, but then it's like, but her sister was there, and she threw something at my head
Well, I don't know about that.
I really don't remember that.
Oh my god.
OK, well, I'm going to have to go in the codex and research
stuff.
I'll have to go in the codex.
Maybe don't go into the code.
OK, I won't do that.
Maybe for his birthday, it's like, delete that from the codex.
Let's delete that.
I'm just going to leave the whole codex.
If you send me a picture, like a band-aid on my head,
I might remember it, you know, but.
I mean, I think it is remember seeing it as is he has the brain like that guy from the
Well, maybe it is thing actually the codex
Thing that is well the codex thinks he's amazing. The codex has
I know the codex is your alice McQueen. I mean, it's like it's confusing you and alice
Well, let's take well, maybe certain. I'll talk to you about that. Okay. We'll talk about
Yeah, wait, did you call her alice McQueen?
No, no, Alex McQueen confused with me because people call me Alex sometimes.
Because one time Alex said, I'm thinking of Steve McQueen.
I'm thinking of Steve McQueen.
That's what I'm thinking of.
The actor from Bullet, he drove that, he drove that Mustang through San Francisco
and all the hills and stuff and like the 70s or something.
That's when I heard McQueen that's why I thought it was the actor from bullet
Well, you're so I guess I know you're not gay because you if you're gay you would have thought I was
Because you know what he's such a man. He's a demand because it's like I've hit on him and stuff. I've got to test everybody
Comfort around anybody of any sexual because he's from the Northeast and he's been around everybody and I have no problem with gay people at all
But for some reason I noticed with gay men, especially gay men,
I feel like it's a goal of theirs to like try and turn straight men.
I want to turn you, but I'm on the radio, but you know what I'm saying?
He's like, I want to turn you.
NorCal said, what did NorCal say?
Like, NorCal is like, he said, oh, I used to love it.
I got a call from a gay guy because there would be cocaine on the table.
Okay, we have Mike.
Wow.
Okay, well, I've.
Listen, I mean, you know, Mike, are we are you joining the party?
Are you gonna have a bottle of alcohol if you're gonna come up?
Okay, he always has a bottle of alcohol.
I've been ribs.
Oh my God.
He's eating a rib.
Well, good.
He's eating today.
Okay.
Oh my God.
I was between us here.
He hasn't been here since.
Really?
months.
Alex, where have you been?
I have a picture.
He might as well.
Come on up.
it's not a doc because this is like an animated thing but this is I got this recently and I
was like I made it a thumbnail Alex and I think well I don't mean to interrupt but LD you look great
thank you Alex you too you look gorgeous you look great thank you but I'm so I'm so happy you
got your house and everything yeah everything settling down
becoming an adult, becoming an adult, this adulting shit is weird.
You've always been more of an adult than you know you have been.
Hey, me and LD got into some fun-ass shit one time.
Oh, when I came out to California with vegan?
Oh, I remember.
No, I will never forget that shit.
Oh my God.
I swear to God, bro.
Remember the vape store guy trying to taze me in shit?
I was like I was like buying cigarettes or a vapor I don't know we're in the vape store
What'd you say
You came on the RV with us to the country music festival, right?
Yeah
I got blackout drunk at a country music festival wearing a Gigi Allen shirt. I stood out like a fucking sore thumb
I end up in like some other
Oh, I got it.
Is there footage of that out there or now?
I just remember Mike telling me to use the magic number.
You got to do three.
Well, I got VIP, dude.
I know that.
Dude, I rolled up to the fucking gate,
and they're like, we don't take cash.
And I was like, what?
And they gave me they gave me they wrote VIP on my fans, dude
I had fucking shipped to the fucking pool party. I had everything all for free dude. Nice dude
My ass rolled up
I was fucking pulled and I made it loose enough to where I could pull it off and I gave it to Manette and vegan
Everybody
No bathrooms at that fucking goddamn level we had the RV thank God so we could piss the fucking RV
Bro, bro, bro, I'm just saying I'm just saying when we're in the event
He had to go like that
it's my birthday. Let's go.
All right, let's go. We're
having a we're having a fun
drinking night tonight.
You know what you boys saw them go outside. I have a cigarette cuz I just had
Yeah, walk the fuck away
I was letting it happen again.
Oh, I shouldn't powder my nose.
You're more feminine than I am.
I'll powder your fucking nose.
Shut up.
I'm old, right?
I'm an old piece of shit.
Oh, I'm older than you are, man.
I've had for like two years.
Yeah.
I probably, I guess I'm the oldest one on this panel.
Oh, my god, dude.
Mike, are you my brother?
I'm like are you in 81? I'm 81.
I'm just, I'm 50, I'll be 55 in two weeks.
But put him back, I gotta make a screenshot.
I gotta make a screenshot.
I'll be 55 in two weeks.
I did it, I did it.
That's my way of doing it.
LD smoking is, hey, hey, hey, you know what they call those, right?
bags, right? They call those fags.
What are you talking about?
I am nice. I am nice. I'm not a dick.
Happy birthday, LD. We got it. We got to do something.
What can we do for you, LD? What do you want for your birthday?
What do you what did do you have a cash app like what's going on?
It's not asking for money it's when somebody wants to buy you a gift they're gonna go spend
Instead be like oh the gift was 1899 they could just give you 20 fucking dollars
Money is the best gift of all I know well he's not gonna let me
I'd rather get like a gift from somebody or something like, you know, then like fucking
Well, I don't need a dress so I can't do a door dash or anything.
I got so many gift cards, bro.
Do you have an Amazon like a wish list that's
Hey, get on my Instagram. Get on my Instagram.
and give me an address to mail a gift card to I'll mail you a phone number.
Do you have any gift cards I have?
Alex I think I still got your number.
Instagram maybe or just I want to I want to do something.
I don't want to say you're obviously any of the number out but
if you want to say the area code say the area code.
I'm a stripper.
I'm a fucking hooker dude.
I'm a prostitute.
Yes.
You got you got me. Okay, so um, what what do I do with the how can I can I do something with phone number? I
Don't think so
LD. Why do you look so distinguished?
Because I'm a gentleman and a scholar.
He's a distinguished gentleman.
He is.
Just hanging out in a fucking bathroom, dude.
Look, here's what you don't know about.
I'm trying really hard.
I just bought a house, dude.
I'm in my garage.
Here's what you don't know.
Yeah, I'm not trying to smoke a house.
Mankave!
gentlemen. This is basically the thing. Yeah. Alex, show your tits. That's what he wants for his
birthday. Show your tits. Shut the fuck up before I put you in front of this shit. Shut the fuck up
before I boot you. You got nice tits, dude. Shut up. I do have the powers. You can't boogie.
LV is fucking cold. LV and I will always say this about him and his family. They're very good people.
Extremely, look at there's the twin bro
All right, I'm gonna go outside of a cigarette. I'll be back. Give me give me like five to a minute something like that
Five or ten, dude
I don't know what you're doing.
Fuck it out.
Five or ten.
Fuck you.
How about take us with you, dude, and let us enjoy the cigarette with you?
You fucking weirdo.
This is my gift for LD.
I'll send this to you if you give me your address, LD.
No, I'm not giving anyone my fucking address.
I want your address.
I want the exact location to your room.
Energy PS coordinate.
LD.
It's not a video call.
There you go.
No, no, LD.
You can at least say you're not in California, are you?
No, I'm on the East Coast.
Yeah
If I was able to if I was able to screenshot like the numbers of a gift card, can you punch him into something and use it?
Yeah, I think scratch off. I guess the pin, you know how they have like this
Shit somewhere. I'm good on that. I'm good. Thank you for the offer
Shut the fuck up. It's a fucking gift, bro, and it's called card
gift
For someone to be the first person to fucking sing me happy birthday is what I'm waiting
Happy birthday to you, happy birthday to long dick, happy birthday to you, did you just stick your ass up for his long dick to enter?
What the fuck was that?
Fucking Christ bro.
Hey look what I have.
And many more on Channel 4.
Yeah. Hey, this is my favorite.
What is that? A marble? Oh, it's actually, you know, have you heard of Oregon?
Oregon is like William Heinrich or something like that.
And he like, it's basically just plastic,
but they fit like all this metal inside of it.
I just heard a whole bunch of letters out of the alphabet that didn't make it.
Yeah, I don't know what that means.
Okay, L.A.P. for SCV.
Hey, how about you take a bath up in my cauldron?
I'm a witch.
Shut up.
I don't think so.
No, no, talk, talk, talk, talk.
My bad, my bad.
Keep going, keep going, keep going.
Mike, Mike is cute, but Mike, you look really good with your beard shape.
Cute.
I want to go snowboarding with you if you can teach me.
What the fuck?
I don't want to go snowboarding anymore.
Is that gay?
Yeah.
It's not gay to teach me how to snowboard.
You just have to touch my butt when you push me.
No, I just...
I mean, I didn't know you're gay, dude.
I'm sorry.
You didn't know?
I didn't know you're gay.
I'm sorry.
I mean...
My asshole is basically just open for the world. I mean he shits pancakes for the rest. Yeah, I mean it's like yeah
I mean the money and silver dollar ones. It's like the big
Can I ask you a question?
Yes, baby. Why do you want to be gay?
It's not like I want to be it's just like
Have you ever been with a woman?
I can't help it.
Well, no, no.
I like dick.
Have you ever fucked a woman, though?
I have.
One time, I put it through one time.
But one thing I did do, I had a girlfriend for three months,
and I put my whole hand inside her vagina,
and it exploded.
And it's like, my whole couch had so soaked.
Yeah, I mean, it was soaked.
And I was like, I don't want to do that again.
I don't want to buy.
So you'd rather stick it in the same sex.
That's better, right?
Well, yeah, you can do it anywhere.
I don't mean women.
I want to meet him dead.
Man is like, oh, here's an anthill.
Let's do it.
Shut up.
Let Eric opinion.
Where's your brother, Eric?
I want to see how you do it.
Fuck you.
You know Eric poo, you know I'm dating squiddy poo and Chris K. wants to move with me
LD LD LD
Move in with you and just shatter bait with me and I'm deadly
Time bro. I used to show him all the time in Vegas
Did
You're trying to make a move on you
No, no, I didn't
No, no, no, no, and you on him on you, you know, I know you're not gay. No, no, never
Said he would like let me penetrate him and stuff. I let him he would let you penetrate him
Fucking news to me. I was just wondering if you would give me a blowjob or I'd give him a blowjob
I figured you're the bottom. He's the top fucking
Hey, but I'm way on top now. I mean, I was like, I'm like climbing the mountain
fucking goat
Man, I'm about to throw up all that Italian sausage I ate.
Do it right in my mouth.
I know I'm so gross, I'm so sorry.
I'm saving myself for Joker.
You're Mr. Extendo Joker.
Yes, sir.
You know Joker?
You really like Joker, huh?
Yeah, I know Joker.
He got me streaming.
He told me to stream.
He told me he's a dude every day.
And I said yes, master.
I've done it every day since.
Yes, master.
He's my master. He's my daddy. He's my streamer daddy and people say oh you groom Joker
I'm like no motherfuckers Joker grew me. They have no idea people are just so confused
He's like in his 20s. I think I don't even know
Yeah, but he told me he told me how to stream and he told me to do it and I did
Hey, guess the card any card. Okay, I'm ace of spades
No, no, we can't be doing the ace of spades dude. Okay. Oh three of club ace of spades three of clubs
No, we can't be doing that either. Okay. Can I get a queen of parts and gunning on a gunning on a gun?
You you said you said the fucking the ace of spades, right? Yeah, you got the ace of spades, right?
is LD and Vegas trolling again?
Hey, you know who controls Vegas?
Those people that actually like, you know.
No, I don't go into the Vegas chat room.
I lived in Vegas.
It was the Ace of Clubs, dude.
It was the Ace of Clubs.
Oh my God, they're kind of similar in my mind.
No, no, you said Ace of Spades, right?
I did, but I said three of clubs next.
So maybe they, you know.
We can, we can.
the ace of spades.
Oh my God.
He's magical.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
We could do that.
But look.
He pulled the seven.
Every card in the deck, right?
Maybe not.
Yeah.
Every card in the deck.
You got every card in the deck.
Clubs three of diamonds. Did you say the three of diamonds? I mean, oh you said three of clubs
Oh, yeah, I had a flurry diamond in the chat. I'm sure you said you said you said you said you said
I'm so drunk. I'm so sorry. Do you have any, um, do you have any, um,
You said three of clubs. Oh shit. You get
All right, I'm back. Hold on. We're doing we're doing card tricks. I mean, this is like it's gone insane in here. It's just fun
It's fun. Well, I didn't guess a card any card. Yeah, we're doing guess a card. You get guess a card, Alex
Wait, what he said he's doing guess a card. He's picking out the card from the deck instantly. Well, I'm I'm mad. Really? Oh, um, I don't know. Um
three of spades
You just do the three of space was that what you just said?
That's what I said.
You want the clubs?
I said three of clubs, she said three of space.
Oh, so you want the three of clubs?
Okay, well, we can make the three of clubs.
She wants the three of space.
That's what I said.
If I mash my hand on it, we can get the three of clubs.
There you go.
Can I mash it with you?
Look at what I have in my hand.
I mean, what card do you want?
I mean, you could say any card.
Yeah, two of hearts, two hearts, two hearts.
I like that song.
All right, can I pick a card?
Go ahead, you do it.
The Joker.
There is no jokers in the deck.
I'm proud of the deck, dude, because it's a 52 card deck, bro.
It's got to be 52.
Oh, my God.
How about the queen of spades, the queen of spades?
Wait, what are we doing, like a card game or like a mental thing?
She was guessing.
He's doing magic tricks.
I'm just asking.
Pick a card.
I'm just saying.
Yeah, queen of spades.
Queen of spades?
Yeah.
Can I make another guess or no?
Yeah, go for it seven of diamonds. I can't do the Queen of Spades though. Why? I picked seven of diamonds
Seven of diamonds. Yeah
Said he wanted to have sex for the nightly literally several times. I think I'm missing a card
I think I'm missing three diamonds.
You take the card.
You're like out of the 52 card deck.
Do you actually only have 30 cards?
Dude, I have to.
I have to.
I'm wondering.
Look, look, look, look.
You said, you said, you said, you said clean, clean of spades,
right?
You said clean of spades, right?
Oh, yeah.
I said three.
He's off the window.
And then I pull out.
The seven of hearts in my mouth.
That's so surprising.
That's very nice.
Wait, how, that came out of your mouth?
That's the dinosaur.
What kind of dinosaur was this?
Okay.
Wait, what do you have in your mouth?
This is the dinosaur right there.
Oh, there it is.
What is that, organite?
I had this one. This is really cool.
It has like this gold.
Yes, a lot of people.
Do you make the Organite site?
I mean, I bought these words a few years ago,
but I would love to make Organite.
You should make the Organite and give it to or sell it to people
because you that that's like your thing.
I mean, the people are so talented, I was like, oh my God, this is like amazing.
Well, it's not so hard.
You got to get the kit.
There's like a kit that you have to get to make it, but your stationery, you could do
it.
I could, I could learn it, but I need like a hot, like a Native American man to like
come in and like, you know, have you ever, have you ever seen a water trick?
Have I ever done what?
Have you ever seen the oil and water trick?
No, the oil and water trick. You've never seen oil doesn't mix. I want to see the trip
Yeah, the oil and water doesn't mix so so we could we could pull up all the aces, right?
So we got all the aces, right?
at all the aces we can take the aces right here we can slap them on the top look at how Mike is with his hands. He's
attractive we can take we can see what he's doing with his hands. He's got a mechanic.
He's got a mechanic.
So we can see LD is going to notice everything because he has that kind of a mind.
I'm in the middle of the deck. Look, he looked over here. He's going to look over there.
Tap him down into the deck. We'll tap him down into the deck. Oh my god.
Yeah, but you're doing illusions.
It's like this. You just go oil and water.
And oil and water. Oil will always flow to the top.
And you made a vinegar edges now, didn't you?
We got one of these.
We got two. We got that. That's about three.
I mean that all the ace is right to the top all tricky tricky tricky watch out for a guy
with the deck of cards you just can't trust yeah right they're making them they're doing
something I tell them it's definitely strange I don't know okay I pick number 33
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
all right so so we're gonna we're gonna pull we're gonna pull a car we're gonna we're just gonna
pull a car we're gonna go we're gonna make some stacks oh my god okay we'll just another card
this one right now is gonna leave alone leave me alone okay so you see three stacks do we see
three stacks we've got three stacks right we've got three stacks mix them mix them right you know
I don't know. What do you want me to do, twerk? I don't know, because what do you want me to twerk?
Thank you, Sam.
Right, I'm cold too, in the middle.
Then you say, oh, fucking, middle to left, take this one,
I'll put it over here, I'll put that one over there.
Doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter, keep going, keep going, keep going.
Guys, this isn't supposed to be a cat, catnip cigar.
It's not supposed to be a cock.
I swear to God.
I'm going to interrupt the trick.
What the fuck is that, Mom?
All right, sorry, I'm too late.
I'm going to interrupt the trick.
I'm so sorry about my book.
L.T., I figured out how to send you a birthday present.
Uh-oh.
So you guys are going to send me a book.
back and you think that loves the cigar Alex not a day. Okay, LD. You have cell right. I'm gonna put this
Yeah, but I don't want money Alex like us. I'm good. Thank you. There's no other way for me to send your birthday present
Alex, it's fine. I don't like honestly
No, it doesn't matter. No, you you you and your family have been very cool and kind to me over the years
I appreciate it, but really you don't need to Alex like I don't well so what I'll have to I don't need to do anything
I'll know I appreciate it
Anything
Screw you. Just tell me
I'm not saying screw you, but you know what I'm saying
If you if you want me to get something with it
Accepted except a gift grace. Thank you. I appreciate it. Thank you, Alex
I'm going to send you this, this is my ball moveable snowman.
Oh my god, that would scare me if I woke up in the middle of the night and
saw that on the way back.
I'm going to be, I want to give you a blow job.
Yeah, great.
He shut up, oh my god.
There's four teeth.
Well, there's like me, actually I have three teeth, I'm missing one.
Let's see how many cars I'm left with.
How many cards do I have? I have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9. I think I have 9 cards.
Okay.
And if I brush this, it's going to be a...
Look at my teeth, they're straight. That's the only thing about me that's straight, my teeth.
You guys didn't want to pay attention to the cartridge.
Okay, burning joint, you better get up here too. I want to see burning joint in his, in his box.
That's carded card decline it if you want, but I don't think you should
Hey, I'll be I'll do the Marilyn Monroe dance, but only in private. Whoa. Thank you
No, y'all y'all y'all understand LD has been very nice to me over the years whereas he could have just
Not been I'm not one for the drama
I just like L.D. and I always like L.D. too, you know, and like Bita was like don't have him on your piano
He's bad, and I was like
Don't even talk about it. Just shut up. I'll shut up, but I always had a bummer panel and he never had a problem
I'm not yeah, I'm not one to start fights like but like I'm also no one's punching bag, you know
And he is
Unfortunately, a Leo scapegoat in a weird
We're capricorns we understand the scapegoat anything like you know, I mean, it's like, you know
You know cat and we just can't be scared about that doesn't scapegoat, too, you know, we're the Saturn's you go
This fucking son is like I like who I like
and in the past you know what my problem was in the past my problem was listening to
Stupid pieces of shit
too much. Yeah
Exactly. Pick a car. You let you let these voices. Oh go ahead. I'm sorry. I picked the old man
I didn't tell me when to stop
Because I picked I picked the car right now. I'm picking guys. I said pick a car. Tell me what to stop now
You ready? Yeah, what is it?
I'm I'm I'm four of clubs. There's there. Look, there's so many. There's so many that you
I'm picking four. That's what you could have chosen. There's so many you could have chosen.
But right back and I didn't fuck. I picked four of clubs. That's what I'm saying. Well,
I think it. I think it right down to the bottom. Oh my God, it is right there. No.
I feel like I'm watching Edward
Norton and rounders.
It takes time for that shit, but
I mean, pick a card in a card.
It doesn't matter.
It's in the black box.
We'll let LD pick a card.
Yeah, pick a card.
LD, you get a car for your
birthday.
This is fun.
Jack of hearts Jack
Art's dude, you're not you're joking, right? You actually use guys
You didn't say you didn't say jack of hearts, bro. You didn't say jack of hearts. Did you I did
Is it not in there? Yeah, no, no, I think I think I think it's there. I think it's there
I don't I just don't know look look look so we got the jack of clubs
Well, that's not good, that's not good, that's not good, that's not good.
Jack of Stades on the base.
We can take this right here and we can peel it, peel it away.
And as we peel it back, dude, there's the jacket.
My God, is that a foreskin, leave it alone.
No, I'm just a weirdo, I'm sorry.
We make the jacket parts, dude, come right up.
There you go, that's very nice.
Thank you. Okay, I'm gonna pull a tarot card. Well, Mike does have magic. I've known that for a while.
I'm gonna pull one oracle card for each of you. Are we gonna have a magic off?
Are we imagining two tarot cards? I have three dimples. I'm technically a witch.
Did you read LD's cards already?
I'm pulling out right now.
He read the actual date, like the worst book for the date.
I'll see if there's someone you need to forgive
or that means to forgive you.
It says forgiveness.
It says, hey, I'll leave that for Jesus.
I'll leave that for Jesus.
I don't really do forgiveness.
Well, you know, sometimes there's a time and place
for everything, as they say sometimes.
And sometimes maybe there's something you regret
or some kind of like misopportunity
or something that you could actually.
make use of it beyond just like, you know, being simple.
Okay, Alexander, you got beginnings, you got beginnings.
It says, don't be afraid to start small.
Because you know, once you get rolling, you know,
whatever you do, you're gonna do a big, it'll get big.
Don't be afraid to start small,
because it's like the best idea is to start small.
A bunch of small wins are better than like a big win,
you know, like it's just, it's a snowball effect,
you know, the smaller the win, like you just,
I got one from my stroke off too, it says weed.
It says weed.
It says, don't tolerate less than you deserve.
In California, I bought an astray.
I bought some record memorabilia.
We, California, was one of the best.
The astray, when you put the cigarette in it,
does the woman's top disappear?
Like you said, astray.
No, that's just a normal astray, and it just has weed.
What?
You see those lighters and I have these lighters. I've seen those lighters to wear that it's like the
That is real magic. I mean magic is spelling spelling is Alex. Alex. What's your favorite ace? What's your favorite ace? Um
I guess ace of hearts my ace of hearts ace of hearts. You really you really want to say the ace of hearts
Yeah, you're joking right well, that's that's what I like it. I like if I had to pick
You know a thing. Oh shit
Oh, there's the ace of hearts.
How are you doing that?
Are you drawing that when we're not looking
and you're having a bad time, right?
No, he's mad.
Well, he's a twin too.
So they have that twin.
These are magical.
Have you seen those Island Boy twins?
What do you think it would be?
OK, so here's the ace of hearts.
What would your favorite one be?
Not the ace of hearts.
What would it be?
Diamonds. Diamonds. Give me that money. Give me that money. The diamonds.
What other one would it be? What other one?
Diamonds. Ace of diamonds.
What the ace of diamonds? You really would love the ace of diamonds.
Boom.
You like the ace of diamonds. Okay, so there's how are you doing that? There's only two left. There's only two left
What would you love? What would you love? Okay ace of spades when acts because a we love the black ace of spades
Well, the ace of spades the ace of spades is the fucking
Yeah, well, that's the most common so all the so all that would be left would be the fucking what ace of what?
It's a base, it's a base, it's a base.
Everything else is gone, everything else is gone, but we can go.
Did we already say clubs or no?
No, the clubs is the last one left.
We're going to go to a club with everybody.
That was awesome.
We love that.
I need magical cards.
Look at you, look at you, twin.
Hey, twin magic. I mean, it's like those twins. I mean, well, they are magical.
There's a few of them in the community. They're there's a few sets of twins. I
was a twin for a while, but he said it wasn't his brother, but
Amazing people that they just are I have I have several twins my family I have
What would be your favorite card
out of all the cards, seven of hearts is like my absolute favorite.
No, no, no, you can't say that you can't.
Well, it just is because I like hearts.
I mean, I like the number seven, so it all coincides.
That's what I like.
Seven of hearts is like can can immersive the seven of cups?
And that's like the acid shirt card.
Yeah, well, it's because my birthday is January 7th and everything about me
from my shoes size to my size of clothing to everything is seven.
That would be like an Alice in Wonderland thing, right?
Well, here's Alice in Wonderland.
My birth is January 7th, too.
I've got a 28-inch waist.
I've got a 28-inch waist, so.
Well, I mean, I'm probably not a size 7 right now,
but my ideal size is size 7.
I'm an extra small a a you can rewind the stream. Did you see the deck the whole time? No, I'm not reminding this
Always make sure that your favorite
Right. Oh my god. This is hot
Thank you
Mike, can you come to my birthday party and do magic tricks all day for me?
Mike, you, me, and whoever else, we should all meet and have a get-together.
It would be so much fun.
I want to do a birthday party for Aldi.
Cheers.
Thank you.
Yeah, dude, this is great.
I'm a magician on my birthday.
This is great, man.
This is your streamer birthday.
This is your streamer birthday, Aldi.
Cheers, everybody.
I love that.
I love that top, Alex, how it's connected through the mid-scene, but is it open in the back or?
No, it's just like in the front, in the back.
Just the shoulder blades?
Yeah, it's a Japanese style. I got it from online. I have it in like five colors.
went crazy. Very cool. Yeah. And I got it. But I like it. But I like this color, this color. You know, even J-Dog said that this is a good color for me.
I appreciate it that really. It is because it's like a highlight on you. Yeah, it goes with me. Yeah. It goes with me.
All right, Aldi, happy birthday. What's your favorite card?
Well, you got to go you got to go ace through ace through fucking King
Okay, hmm
love spades
You know, do you know, do you know what the word actually comes from the French card set where that where they actually designed that from?
No, it comes from the calendar. There's four seasons. So each suit represents the season
there are
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I want the one where he's shown his dick and I was like that was me. I was me asking you that I want that
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What like the new?
One that can be shown as somebody with a dick is the one who's stabbing himself in the head
That's the suicide king. That's the suicide king. I don't know. I never mind. I'm not involved in the conversation
Yeah, that's the suicide king. Oh my god suicide king. Where's the dick? I don't see the dick
It's just a regular card.
I can't see you. Let's see that beautiful face. Oh, there he is here. Oh my god. He looks like a
What is that? What do you have a beer like Charles Vance him? They're scaring me. No
He looks like he's got a whole bunch of deer heads in his house though. Oh, yeah, he does. I've seen him on his garage
I knew it. I knew it
He also he also jogs in his underwear and in the military breakfast. I love it
No, it's here.
Oh my god.
Hey, we're having a fun night tonight.
I was in our Queens here, they're the creme de la creme.
Hey, that's what we are.
Ace?
We are the cream of the crop here.
Is nobody going to guess their favorite ace?
Okay, I'm going to guess ace of hearts.
Ace of hearts?
Yeah.
I'm going to guess ace of diamonds.
No, you're fucking not, dude.
No, you're fucking not.
You are not going to guess the ace of hearts because guess what?
Oh.
It's the two of clubs.
Oh, no.
Ooh.
But the two of clubs went in to the ace of clubs.
I feel like we're like in Vegas or Monte Carlo or something.
Are you counting cars, Mike?
I mean, it's like, are you?
Yes, he is.
Well, I'll take you to Vegas and stuff.
How do I count?
Am I going to count?
You guys are making random guesses.
No, but I'm saying counting cars like she didn't gambling.
Yeah, I do know that, but I don't do that.
Well, that's what Blackjack, that's what Blackjack is.
I go like this they three people playing and I'm like oh boom. I got a six. Oh, there's an 18
We got a four four. We got 14. So this is a low card. So you're gonna you're gonna obviously everyone's gonna stay
My brother down at a table anywhere in Vegas anytime of the night and always
Fisherman, what are you saying you burning joy everybody loses
lose, lose, lose, dealer wins.
It has always wins.
All right, so forget about this.
I have to interview LD for his birthday.
OK, I'll show you.
LD, so what do you have planned for 2026 to 2027 being
the age that you are now?
Well, I'm not 26 to 27, but for the year that it is.
Well, that's what I mean.
Yeah, 2027 to 2027.
I've been doing a lot of work on the house.
I'm having my kitchen remodeled in like a week.
Awesome.
Easy case.
I'm going to redo a couple of the rooms myself.
Oh, really?
My sunroom, my bedroom.
Yeah, I want to do the flooring and paint and stuff like that.
I want to work on that.
Are you going to have like a study or like a home office,
or do you have like two beds?
I've got two bedrooms, but I don't even
know what I want to do with the second.
I'm not even in my bedroom.
I literally have my bed in my living room,
You know, it's just easier being a living you're used to being in like I totally get it
Like if you're used to being in a small space and then something big space
You're like what the hell am I gonna do with all the space?
so
Okay, well, maybe make your second bedroom like a multi-purpose room
Well, like if you have guests over it can maybe maybe like a Murphy bed
on one wall, even though I keep making it like your office
or creative room, because you're very creative.
I know you like to do your art and you know whatever else
it is that you do, but when you have your guest over,
you know, your niece, you're your guest over.
Well, I think I want to, yeah, keep the guest room,
because like my garage, I had a company come out
and I want to see how much would be to epoxy the garage,
the floor.
So, they told me it was going to be three friends.
They told me it was going to be three friends.
I go, I'll do it my fucking self.
I was going to say you should do it yourself.
Because you're skilled enough.
I know how you are.
You put an LD on your forehead?
You could do it.
Yeah.
Because LD is like a master of all trades.
What's your favorite queen?
Me.
I'm his favorite queen.
No, what's your favorite queen?
You already you already gave me shit for my feelings. I was under mayors
No, no, because I know you have a heart, bro. I like African Queens
You have a heart. Yeah, cuz that fucking Queen of Diamonds goddamn gold digger
Well, it's okay as long as he has her own diamond. He has his own money. He doesn't have to worry about that
Oh
Yeah, I really want to use it
I really want to use it to like fix up the house like that was in good condition. Don't get me wrong
But like I want to make it like you'll make it like I want to paint the walls fucking dark purple and like burgundy
Shit like yeah
I don't care I've got a sunroom
I have a sunroom in the front and I'm like well you're gonna paint it dark colors because like you're just gonna try to spawn
LD's northeast
He's a northeastern kind of guy. He's been in the west coast before he
Like when I think about LD I like I know I shouldn't say it like this
But I but like when I met LD in person. He showed me graffiti art in Las Vegas. So I always think of like
like a piece of Frank kind of
stuff when I think about LD,
but in a like, even like the
two paintings I had those done
in Vegas of my back. I've
already seen very least of
Frank. Yes, and that's LD.
LD is super masculine, but he
is super artsy and artsy. I
was supposed to the arts.
I was supposed to get it.
He died November 11th on Veterans Day, he fell down the stairs and broke his tibia in three places.
How old was he?
He was 11.
I was just going to say literally three or I was just going to say.
My condolences and he's in heaven, he's in dog heaven.
I went on Sunday to a Greyhound rescue where they do like, because I've always had Greyhounds.
Are you going to get another one?
of course of course so I went to the Greyhound rescue but they didn't have any males all they had were females
wait no wait wait wait until they have another male if you want a male
yeah so I told them I don't want dark brindle I want it like three to four years old
you know fresh from the racetrack whatever and I went to the farm to go visit it and they're like
yeah we only have females I went I came home Monday they called me they're like oh we've got a male
He's a fawn that you want to come back and meet him.
I mean, that's the perfect dog for you.
It's named Tony Montana.
I mean, I don't do cocaine, but yeah, I like the name Tony.
I do like the name Tony.
The kind of guy that you are.
That's your dog.
Hey, hello.
What do you mean by your feet?
Well, I see feet.
This is weird.
I don't want to see what he's going to do.
He's going to die.
Don't ruin us.
Don't ruin us here.
It's like a belly flop dive.
Fucking hell.
That's what the guys do.
And everyone's like, full screen him.
We used belly vlog guys, didn't know they'd die.
I see him, no, I don't even make stuff up.
That was not a good dive.
We saw him and we're not impressed.
I mean, I'm trackable.
Well, he wants to show off tonight.
Let him show off.
But in his veto, if you want to show off tonight.
Well, if we need to call 911, we will.
Hopefully he makes it back to the ladder.
Who?
I need a nine.
but hopefully there he is he's okay he's not even are you okay and jackable i see he's all right
he's mad i want to be like tell him to stop that though because i don't want to have the
anxiety god ass the anxiety jackable i know this is a worry i don't know what you're doing i hope
there's a lifeguard on duty no there's not he's i will i will that's probably his property honestly
I don't know where he lives.
He's wrestling alligators.
Really, really psyche you're going to be Baywatch.
Are you going to be David Hasselhoff?
No, I'm going to be Pamela Anderson.
He's going to be Obi.
Oh, okay, Pamela.
He's going to be the little boy.
Name a card any card Alex any card? Oh me?
Six of
Clubs really are you joking you're just serious. Okay. Oh, I saw I saw I just there
How are you doing this shit, man?
Are those trick cards?
How are you doing that?
Was that really the Six of Clubs?
It looked like it.
Was it the Six of Clubs card?
How do you do that?
I don't know.
That's crazy.
I mean, you could say any other card.
Roll through I feel like he gets better at the drug. What are you funny? I do have a I mean it's again
There was some a car trick if you want to see a car trick this guy
I would go for his girlfriend, and he's like it was like to her family. He's like I want to do a car trick
And the family was like
Wait, wait, wait, wait, Rick works
Let's see it. Let's see it. I show it in another card
Uh, where are you untrackable?
Don't tell us.
Eight of what?
You know like it probably is the kind of guy here. I didn't see anything. Was it a bicycle wheel?
What's going on? Hard trick works dude. No, that's the ladder that's the ladder to the pool. Yeah, that's not a pool
Eight of what?
That's a lake. That's what?
Guess what?
What what what is he's doing? He's he's a nature guy. Hey, okay, but you just said but you just said but chicken butt
Yes, well, he's a he's a nature. What would have been the energy him I
Before you do it's like
It's the aid of art
But if you spell but
You oh, this is
There's the aid of diamonds.
If you're also like that.
Hey, I want to see your butt sometime.
Stop it, Scythe.
You like butt?
I like butt.
I like the butt.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
I mean, I'm just not through nothing, not nude.
I mean, it's like through short.
No, stop.
Oh my God, there you go.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
Woo, I remember the pass out.
All right, all right, all right.
Yes, now.
Gotta get your card, LD.
What do you got?
Ten of diamonds.
You're so stupid. You're so stupid.
Wait, you took this camera off of fucking.
I'm going to fix it. There you go.
There you go.
I was sitting here trying to go like this and go.
Stop.
Do you have a flirty of diamonds in the deck?
That'd be interesting.
There you go.
Very good.
I'm not going over. I'm not
going over Mike's house for any
poker games anytime soon. Me
either. I'll go there. His
brother. Royal flush. Mike I
want to talk not to play any
games. Show he's giving he's
doing a lap dance for what's
Hey, I'm trackable your favorite a's fuck the mustard mustard. What's this?
Okay, what's your favorite number on trackable? We're talking to you. I don't think you can hear us
your favorite eight. It's either a one or eight. It has it. It says to be the diamonds, clubs,
spades or. No, I'm sorry. You asked me my favorite number. I got married on Friday. I got married
on Friday the 13th. Oh my god. Wow. In 2013. So, so you can kiss my whole ass. Ask me my
favorite number and then say it's not good. It's not good stuff.
Okay. Wow. Well, okay. Okay.
for untrackable. I'm going to
pick this card. His. Okay.
Friday the 13th. 2013. I'm
going to pick diamond. Um is
favorite. Four of diamonds for
untrackable. No, no, no. It
wasn't a number. It was an
ace, but no, I I picked four
diamonds for untrackable.
Or diamonds that doesn't work really. No, I think I was asking for the ace
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, look.
Can I have a diamond?
No, no, because look, because look.
No diamonds for you, Psychic.
I thought I was gonna get a four of diamonds.
But it ended up being the four of diamonds.
My God.
But then I said, wasn't it the-
We're all gonna come out wasn't it that I say yes, I asked for an ace
You're walking through snow. What's going on here? No, it's sand. I think it's sand. No, there's stones. Those are still
No, I
Thought it was sand that we saw but he wants a 13 dude
There ain't no like a king a king a king is like a 13
Well, I guess, I guess a king could be a 13.
A king could be a 13.
Well, wait, I don't think there's any 13 in a card of decks, right?
No, but if you go one through 10, one is the ace, 10, and then you've got 11 jacks,
well, queen, 13 king.
There's a great one for you.
Rick, you do, and the king is the 13, the queen is a 12, the jack is an 11, and then
it goes down with the ace.
Okay.
So when you count up, you count up from 8th to 10th, and X is 11th, Queen is 12th, King is 13th.
All right.
You're too young for you, Mike.
Oh my god.
Sound check. I said I like it figure out for a few moments
Just a few moments. I say a car before you leave
Say a card before I leave yeah, I'll say
Let's see something obscure eight of diamonds
Diamonds no, but I got it. No, I'll pick something else wait. Did you show it eight of diamonds? No, it was the eight of spades. Oh
I'm into this fucking right. Okay
Okay, now. Okay guys, now we can take our clothes
Is it time yet?
I think I've lost everybody she wanted that aided. I want that eight Mike. Good eight bro. It's right there. Oh
Fuck I got my phone
Hi, Nick of time. Hi for everyone. Hey, Alice McQueen, shout out something in the chat
I mean, I mean I'll pull another car for the chat. Let me see who we have here. We have a
Mike stroke off Mike broke off. Okay
You want a mermaid, Mike?
I'll give you a mermaid.
Mike, you got that shoes wisely card, okay?
So you do need to make a choice,
but you need to make the right choice.
It says, be discerning.
You don't have to keep,
you don't have to keep everything in your net.
Okay, so choose wisely. You don't have to take everything. You have to discern, right?
So there's something you need to choose from. Okay, and then I have run trackable. I have safety
So in trackable, you need to put on those little floaties by the side of the pool and get in that raft
It says don't be too proud to go back to shore
Okay, and then we have LV you get one more you your mermaid card is and I love mermaids
So you have flow it says let your worries drift away
So anything you're worried about, just let it float away.
Because put it, chuck it in the bucket, bucket, as I like to say.
This is great, Alex.
Alexander, you can get the fuck out of here.
Come on.
I want a big group hug with all these guys.
I just got naked all of a sudden.
I love it.
This is my dream show.
Why has my show always been like this?
All I wanted was Mike naked on my show the whole time.
So Mike, you're still out in California, I assume?
No, I live I live in Antarctica now. Oh my god, do you have
I'm going to Sacramento in October. Yeah, barbecue penguin. I want to hear ours from me where I'm at Cali
I'm I'm going to Sacramento in October for aftershock
Nice, dude. Maybe I should make a journey up there
Dude, if you had tools fucking play in the festival
You say tool fuck. Yeah. Yeah, fuck. I want to go buy some of fucking Maynard's goddamn wine
I heard he's got a winery in California. I want to buy some that fucking wine. Oh
Yeah
So me and my friend are flying out to Sacramento in October
What card is this?
Show me like Bob Rogers show me the edge and I'll tell you what card is the other side not the other the
Vertical side the vertical side
Hopefully it's a water
It's not gonna be the card you're thinking of probably I'm thinking nine of clubs
No, it's not
Not even close
Can't even flip through enough to fucking do it
Well, you have to like flip through like this and shit and like you'll you'll slip you'll slip it and then you'll just be like
white
Right and you should be like, oh
The way the way that you're holding the way that you're holding the deck of cards is called a mechanic grip
Have you ever heard of that like pinky break you do pinky breaks? Yeah, there you go
And then fucking and then you could you could do a folded corner
You can do a full to you can base deal off the bottom. Yeah, but but you could do a full corner like that
Obviously the break and I can always keep it like this to where it looked at deck
But then you'll always see the brakes and then I can be like, oh my clubs
You guys want to go to a club? Let's get a party busing last night
Action on a party bus, bro, and the guy does a lot of cocaine did so it'd be fun
I love cocaine. I'll do it, but I don't like the fucking I don't buy it. I just I'll do it. Yeah, I mean, I don't buy
I remember the last time I met Mike in real life
He had DMT and I smoke DMT for the first time and I was like, whoa, bro like
Well, the question is did you stroke off with them?
the DMT. No, no weird shit. I mean, it's like, why do we remember me and vegan, we're just
doing hits of DMT, and we're just like, holy shit, dude, all of LA smells like DMT. Listen,
listen, I had like the DMT pens, I had the DMT pens. Listen, listen, listen, just check
the other night, dude. And she had a lot of money. And I was like, fuck dude, I was like,
Why oh, I was like we get all the money and not worry about it because if we did I did I did I did fucking
Cocaine and meth and Adderall and ketamine and ecstasy
Spend all the money and then it's like you're
At the end of the night, she's like I want to fuck and I was like
I have a special request Mike
One time with your ex-girlfriend and a dog tell the story
What you told us or what happened with your ex-girlfriend you were in bed and the dogs were from the bed and did something and tell the story
Oh, it wasn't an ex-girlfriend. It was just some chick. I fucked on tinder
Like porno tits I think would you like to wake up to these every morning? I'm like
Big-ass titties. I mean, I don't really care about big tits. Honestly. I think big old fat giant ass
Fucking 300 pound fucking dumb bitch. She was cool
She had fat girl titties.
I jumped in the bed, bro.
And I was like, can you get your dog?
Can you put your dog out of the room?
Dude, a motherfucking dog jumped up, bro.
I was pounding her, bro.
And started licking my asshole.
Dude.
I was like, what the fuck?
That's so funny.
He's so cute.
I thought, hey, it's like, it goes up.
It starts like licking her in the face.
I'm like, too.
This is fucking.
What kind of dog was it?
Like like a choweenie, bro
Doverman or something
It was a canine Belgian Malinois, and he was searching for
Narcotics in your butt look it came up and took a lick and seven inches went into my
I was like, that was Mike selling the story, I didn't do anything about a dog licking my
asshole.
I didn't do it on her show and now she's going to say it again, take a little puppy pup.
What the fuck dude?
I was sitting there pounding away.
And I I busted all quick. Well, I didn't bust quick did I pull a little perform
But I was like finishing on her. She's like you don't mind if I pull up my little friend to finish the job
And I was like, are you talking about your dog?
You better not be the dog
I pulled out her dildo dude. Oh my god
How big was it Mikey? How big and how many did you do? How many inches?
And then I started just finishing her off with her purple fur
Oh, it was kind of funny and then I had to meet her parents in the morning. That was oh
Look to be there to begin with we went to her friend's house and you're shaking
You're shaking her dad's hand with her fucking dried pussy juice on your fucking fingers. Yeah
Awkward
Let's make it freak off with broke off broke off
Do you want to go to freak off with me and Alexander McQueen? We'll be naked
Alexander's been gone for a long time. I know he left me but now he's back because he's my he's my boyfriend
No, Alexander's been gone. I'm gonna leave him. He's in there trying to rub one out, dude. It's not working. I don't care
One hour again
Okay, Alex, you say yes, I mean Donald in the way. I don't I don't even know. I don't
I don't anything I may have a meal at once a year
I think she I think she wants to go smoke a cigarette. I need a cigarette, too
Give thanks to Alex for never sending me one dollar and providing you guys with so much love doing
He's never given me a dollar once and I've never prepared for one. Oh my god, dude
Is this still here? Why are you such you my Mike? Why are you so cute? Oh, why haven't I noticed this before I just drunk?
I'm a fucking look at someone told me I had OG geezer merch the other
It's beautiful dead, man.
It's not fucking OG, geezer, merch.
I thought it was cool.
What is it, what is it though?
It's just a Jerry Garcia hoodie from like a show.
Oh, Jerry Garcia.
Yeah, Jerry.
Did he die?
He's been dead a long time.
He died on my birthday, dude.
August 9th, which my birthday's coming up in two weeks,
dude, August 9th is my birthday.
Oh, you're a Leo too, bro.
Cheers, man, cheers.
Let's fucking go, Leos, bro.
Hey, I'm a Leo North note, and that means.
My kid my kids at the end of the month. I think he's like a Virgo or some shit, but but we have the same first month
Yeah, I can't my kids an adult now, dude
You guys gonna see a picture of ghosts?
Not really
There he is. Oh, there he is. Oh my god. He literally entered the student is exactly what I said that I'm psychic
I'm psychic. I'm fucking psychic ghosts. You're there
Literally put that you appeared
I'll take it down. Oh, no. And now I know what you do behind my back. I'm really good at this.
I know what you do behind my fucking back. You look like a good asshole because I love you.
I literally defend you. I'm getting drunk to be on the show. I'm sorry. Damn.
I literally defend you, but you want to say you're in touch shit. Why do you run?
No, come back. Don't run, Pussy. Come back. You want to talk shit behind my back?
We got on it. I'm glad I did join.
Ghost gets a card in a car
Why don't you take that card and shove up your ass? I don't give a fuck about your card
All right, then whatever man. Have fun with that. I find having that existence beautiful mindset
Kidding you're good looking look at how cute you are
Who goes that's ghost well when I when I made that AI rendering of him
I thought he actually looked pretty like nice
Don't give you dumb ass excuses no one believes it. We don't care. We don't believe it
I'm gonna tell y'all something funny. I've had so many animals visit me lately because of where I am
I saw hummingbird the other day
That's like a positive omen, but just now I went outside and
There was this the cutest and I know you guys are gonna think it's gross
But I don't think it's gross a little skunk like I think it was like I like skunk like a teen skunk
I don't think it was full white, but but not a baby
Why I've seen it. I've seen it like twice now
and I think it's it almost waits for me to come outside to have a cigarette because I saw it
and it was just like hi here I am oh that's chunks are very cute that's my that's my yard
you know a house you know another few turkey vultures a whole bunch of turkey vultures in my yard
I don't know. I don't know.
I was staying in a place and it was actually relative of mine's property and I went outside
early one morning like the sun was just coming up and I saw this I thought it was cat and I was
like oh that's a nice little cat and then all of a sudden it got on his little legs and and I saw
I don't know. Oh there's. What
of those deer. Yeah dear little
baby deer they're just walking
down. That's a baby. I'm outside
having a cup of coffee like. So
one time in my apartment like
you know. Dude they show up
right right right in front of
my house to. Well that means
that they feel safe that's good
that's not a bad thing I think
they told me they told me they
But it was like a hundred degree day out one day and I'm like, well, yeah, I can't feed them back water.
told me it's a thousand dollar
So I left them like a five gallon pail of water now every day in front of my fucking house.
They're always going to come over.
They're going to come over.
I had a feeling they're not dangerous.
They're not dangerous.
Well, yeah, of course not.
Yeah, they just they just eat my fucking bushes and you know, like.
Well, they but they that's not sure at all.
Dears are they can be they can be dangerous.
They can be dangerous.
They're like the front of my house in my house goes. What is the last?
What do you say site what are you talking? What do you say? What's the latest? What's the last bush you a ghost?
Don't you know what at this point don't ask me no dumbass question sir
Leave ghost you little bitch. Why would you leave? It's your panel. Why would you leave?
It's supposed to be one of your friends. What were you just doing? What were you just doing when I joined?
I don't want to argue with you tonight. It's not even I don't want to argue with you those why are we arguing a couple?
We're not even dating. I never even had sex with you. I mean, just your penis once I
Asked like a bigger card you brought up to gay shit
Stop coming back and coming at same time. You want to handle?
Mike is a magician
Mike Mike has Mike has I guess the power of card magic, but Mike has the power of woman magic
I have noticed this about you. I thought those were care cards yours take notes
I'm not gonna lie to you. Yours is woman magic because even I I mean
No, you continuously talking shit about me. So I just leave it alone.
This is what you look like. This is what you look like right there.
Oh, that's true
That doesn't work one day and there was a raccoon
stretching at the door, his little baby raccoon.
You got me, Sike, you won that debate.
I love how I did it.
I'm just not familiar with the raccoons.
I never grew up in an environment
where there were a lot of raccoons.
But I do like them, but their little hands
freak me out that they just do.
Are you I saw I saw a video they what what raccoons do is they'll take their food and they'll dunk it in water to like make sure
It's clean or whatever really. Yeah, so I saw this video where
They gave they gave the raccoon cotton candy they gave the raccoon candy and it takes us like oh, no
Dunks it in the water and it disappears and he's like
What is your what the fuck happened with the shit you gave me like I think that raccoons
Maybe they're like a like like a stage of evolution for something like because they do have the little yeah the squirrel
They have like they have they have opposable thumbs. Yeah. Maybe they're like a stage of
revolution and maybe I like when they take out food and they run on their back legs like human
to take off running. Well they take care of their little babies like if you if you have ever like
seen how they they really take really good care of their little babies that they really do. Yes.
So do possums.
So, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so
I
Have two cards for Alexander this is serenity is not the serenity
He says you quiet days. Yep, the rustling leaves in the distance and enjoy
Ace of hearts
Okay, that's so funny, you know, I'm listening. Yeah, it's joy and serenity. You're a bullshitter things and then enjoy
Yeah, I just tried to make you fucking flash. I flash. I'll tell you psych
A magical panel tonight, okay, do it again, Mike, and I'll believe you if you do it one more time
Let me guess another card two of clubs
We're getting entertainment with the cards from Mike now. We're getting annoying
Wasn't it I love it. You really think you're good. She usually magic is made. I love it
It wasn't the two of clubs I thought I thought I asked to figure out he said yeah, I was talking to him
How's that being annoying or no?
I was really hoping you would sing me happy birthday like Marilyn Monroe.
I was going to do that.
I'm not going to do that.
Happy birthday.
Mike, Mike, Mike already sang it to me.
Everybody, well, everybody sing happy birthday to Eldie.
They did, they already sang it.
Well, I have to shoot for myself?
I'll shoot right there.
Well, I'm just going to do it.
I'm just going to do it. I'm drunk enough.
Saying that shit.
Happy birthday, LD.
Happy birthday to you, and I hope you have every single wish that you want to come true.
Take a shot, please.
Happy birthday, LD.
To you.
I don't know if you just caught that bro, but I just pulled every two in your motherfucking sheet there's only four
I wanna- Mike, Mike, I wanna see you do fucking magic tricks with magic cards.
You got any magic cards in there?
Yeah, ghost is magical things to my butt.
He wanna- he wanna-
Okay, I'm back.
Hold on.
I can't hear you.
What do you want?
Hey, no, no, no, no, no.
What do you just say, psyche?
What the fuck do you just say?
What do you just call me?
Hey, I said ghost is magical things to my butt.
No, you said I'm so fucking what?
I said you do magical things my butt you said I'm so fucking retarded
you do magical things to me
you literally play that shit back you literally said so fucking retarded
play that shit back
oh my god those shit in my mouth
don't blame me I'm just a guest
don't call me retarded
not the one either dude that's not the one either dude
but the two of fucking diamonds that was
oh I got a pile of salt
The two green a mix. I'm good. No. No. Alex, you got to do Taheen on Margarita. Fuck salt. You got to do Taheen.
Well, I don't have any Taheen. I don't even know what Taheen is.
It's that red Mexican spice. They do the simple spirit.
Because it's like spicy when you drink them. It's really good. When you drink the Margarita rather than having the salt, you do the Taheen because it's like spicy.
Let me make a note about that because I don't know what that is.
Yes, sir.
If you're in California, if you're in California, you've definitely had to I'm out west. I'm not in California, but I
So it's like a red Mexican goes what you remember you came over to the original with me. That's a picture of a ghost
Remember just call me fucking Riccardo. I just show pictures
Alex
I've seen it before yes, I have yeah, it's so it's so much better than salt. It's so much better
I'm a little fancy with the Himalayan salt I do and normally I put it on the rim of the glass
But yeah, I didn't have time to hang out with y'all right now
I'm too
A little bit spicy though or no
Yeah, but you need sugar, you need the sweet with it though, not the spicy, you need the
sweet.
Well, what I'm saying is they typically do salt, there's no sweet, it's salty and rather
unsanitary.
Are you Hispanic?
Just get Mexican ice cream, it's fried ice cream and just put a hot sauce all over it.
L.D. is Italian.
I think he's like Sicilian or something.
Forget about it.
I'm a pizza bagel, I'm a pizza bagel, I'm half Italian, half Jew.
Oh my gosh. Well that's why it's so good looking that's why it's good. I leave I leave I leave a really
Ask for it back. L.D. is a good-looking guy
Alex can you repeat that please? Can you repeat that L.D.? I just said it L.D.'s. He knows. He knows I think it's good.
Alex is great-looking too. I mean Jesus like come on
I know L.D.
Y'all don't know the history, but they're a good-looking family, okay?
They're a good-looking family.
Is it a crime family?
We are a good-looking family.
Are you part of the mafia, bro?
Goose is like the grandmother. I'm not
Tattooed across my chest
Stop leaving if you're gonna say something stay up here
Hey ghost you want to get one word in and then leave no fuck that how you gonna
say one word then leave they come back let's say after like five minutes
they say another word after everyone drop it and say another word then leave
and then come back after five after we already dropped it then say another word
if you want to argue let's I'm not even argue if you want to talk let's talk you
don't have to run
You don't eat it was fucked up. That's what you're running
That should go
Take it down a couple notches.
Yeah, there you go.
Look, look, that's my, that's my, that's, look, LD.
That's my, that's my credentials.
She has not aged one fucking day.
I have, I have, I have makeup does wonders.
And makeup does wonders.
That was five years ago.
You look younger too.
Alex, come on.
You're in that photo than you do now.
You are so sweet. Oh my god. You don't look you don't look you don't look a day over beautiful on that one
You know who's responsible for it NorCal
Was he?
Yes.
Well, it was because he was the one, because I was on Fremont Street in the Vegas area in Nevada.
Yeah, I live right there.
He was right down the street and NorCal was the one who told me that he told you or whatever.
But we had we had the pizza at this awesome. It was like I don't know the name of evil evil cannibal bar. It's called
We we had pizza we had drinks we walked around
Ld you know we had so much and I gotta tell you age horribly, bro
I know
Younger now than he did
I don't know. I don't know.
L. D. took the risk and we had so much fun and that I love I love meeting up with people. I love
Yeah, and I always liked your mom your mom is freaking awesome. She's always been so kind to me
And
She really does
Sorry stop doing that. You're gonna burn your fucking ass. I'm doing that
I don't know you're gonna bring yourself some of them, but I kind of am familiar with them and I consider them like
Distant cousins or it's funny. It's funny because like like I met you
Did you ever you ever meet Jen in real life? I've never even had a conversation. I think it's so funny
I think it's so funny that like
you've probably talked to my mom and my sister probably more than me
but me and you have actually met up in real life like me and you have actually met up in real life
i know i know well that's why i mean i i know jim thinks what she thinks but i really do care
about whatever you know and i'm so i'm i'm really happy that she has gone to and i and i don't even
care about any of the misunderstandings or bygones or anything like that
I just, I'm so proud of her.
First thing that is, she is strong, so strong.
But you saved her.
I've seen you in two circumstances.
Save her.
If she might not admit it, I don't care.
I know what you did.
And people don't get this about you.
LD is the best big brother
somebody could have possibly.
Yeah.
That's debatable.
She was in.
When she was in Vegas, can we get Ghost off here?
Because he doesn't get it.
Ghost, you fucked up.
I'm not being mean, but he doesn't know.
Ghost, no.
You don't know.
Well, explain to me.
Well, I'm telling you what.
I'm the best big brother.
I was going to protect him, though.
My sister got knocked up by, like, a YouTube
streamer who was abusing her.
And I was living in the same town in Los Angeles.
You were gonna kill him. He's lucky you didn't Vegas that she was and I chased that I took them out of Las Vegas
That I go. I will come here every fucking day
What people don't know is that LD embodies a tremendous
Amount of restraint. He is a legitimate bad ass. He rides motorcycles. He's been an
Oh, what do you call it, an EMT?
He's been a firefighter.
He wants your medical profession.
He can heal you, but he can kill you.
That is the reality.
I'll bust your shit open.
I'll bust your shit open and get you close.
He will heal you, but he will kill you.
But I'm not saying that you're gonna kill anybody,
but you know what I'm saying.
That is the reality of LD.
No, I fucking...
And don't get mad when I say this LD, but you already kind of know it, but I'm going to say something.
Don't get mad. It's just the spirituality of me.
No, it's the way...
You remind me of somebody screaming at me on the Bible.
You might say, oh, please.
When I look at you, LD, I think you're like Moses Young.
It's hot. It's hot stuff.
The way I look at it, I go, no man, no man should pick up your hands to a woman.
No, no real man should ever pick up his hands to a woman.
So if this motherfucker is going to pick up his hands to my sister,
I'm going to murder this motherfucker.
Don't kick his ass.
I'm going to be right on you, dude.
I'm the fuck out of Vegas.
Power of God.
She moved out of Vegas before I did, like for real.
I was like, I'm gonna show up here every fucking day until I see him outside and I will fucking stomp him out
I will stop his I will stomp his guts out on the curb
And you did stop it you did you put you put you you suppressed the energy
I had a move they moved they moved to Oklahoma
They moved to Oklahoma and then he broke his mom's shoulder and got another felony charge in Oklahoma
how well things turned out your sister is happy so good i'm so happy yeah everything looks wonderful
no one she's doing so good she's doing i'm so proud i'm so proud of my sister and you better
believe i'm gonna shut that bitch down you like you don't even know dude i heard i heard let's
You already know I've never let's not speak on it, but what I am saying is that there is a certain alliance
LD oh
No, god damn. Hi, Alex
Naturally but
Yeah. Yeah. You do. You do.
You know, I can't. I can't.
I can't. I can't. I can't say
about LD. You can you can come
for me because. Yeah, the only
thing I just wouldn't admit.
I just wouldn't admit. I just wouldn't
admit. I just wouldn't admit. I just wouldn't
Yeah, but I like Alex a lot more than Noel, so he is.
He's right.
Hey, you don't treat her like that.
You should or you're good.
No, stop it.
I can't deal with it.
Very disrespectful, man.
He just comes on here to start some shit, like.
Oh, I came up here to start some shit when I first joined what happened boyfriend is lucky. I said no, well
She saw my dick one time and she just can't get off the motherfucker
She's coming up on stream
Ever seen that movie the other guys
I didn't I didn't show it to you I didn't show it
We've always had a very respectful friendship, you know
everybody should date L. D.
if L. D. was single, I never I
never did. I would totally everyone.
I can hear a magician. You make
the magician leave. If I didn't have
a guy in my life, I would so go for
L. D. Oh, so you're good. Must
L. D. is hot. He is smart. He is successful.
He has better hair, better beard, better eyes.
You're in a committed relationship now, Alex?
I am.
Good for you. Good for you.
Honestly.
I'm monogamous to this.
Good, good.
He's actually weird.
If things go wrong, I'll chase your ass.
L. D., can you hear me now?
I mean, if things go wrong, you know, you got my number.
I think it'd be really funny if I showed up to a fucking family, you know event or function
Alex with me like I even I think I joked with you
Can you get it out of her system?
She could beat the shit out of a letter.
I can't even fucking hear Mike at this point.
I would let her do it.
But I really, I really, if I were to go for LD,
like you don't even believe, LD is marriage material.
Everyone knows this.
You don't want to marry me.
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh, I'm sorry.
Because you know because it's a really nice dick you want to see
No, not everybody but
I get fucked up. Ghost, I get fucked up and I like to party, you know, like fucking...
You get fucked up and like to show your dick? That's called sexual harassment. That's what you're spying on, though.
I'm not here slut-shaming you, ghost. Like, who kills me?
Let me tell you something interesting.
It's not slut-shaming, brother. It's, uh, that's sexual harassment, if you want to charge.
That's not slut-shaming.
I so wish Ghost was shut up.
Okay, I'm...
Okay.
And just from what I know, and it's going to sound horrible, what I'm about to say, I think that
LD missed his calling. I think that LD should have been the porn star instead of Jen.
That's my opinion, and I will never say it again.
But that's what I think, because LD does, LD has, and I'm not going to say how I know, maybe I don't know.
Maybe I was too busy serving our country, I was too busy serving our group home.
Maybe I still know, but LD definitely has the appropriate equipment.
I love it. LD, after the show?
No, LD is not allowed.
No, I'm bringing girls back in.
No, I'm protecting LD, unless LD breaks out of jail.
I am not gay. I am not gay. I've had three sons with other dudes. I've swapped with them. I am not gay, dude.
LD could be the Sicilian hybrid of Lexington Steel.
I was a firefighter.
LD could be the Jewish Sicilian hybrid of Lexington Steel. I will say that and I will never deny it.
He's gonna say I wasn't a firefighter.
Yes, I was a firefighter.
And then he's got the equipment to go with it.
So if you're a woman, now you have the official voucher.
I know.
But now that I'm getting older, I don't have the energy.
That's the problem.
It's like, I've got the equipment.
That's not a bad thing.
No, that's not a bad thing.
I'm gonna have two Red Bulls.
How much energy do you need?
How much energy do you need, really?
Seriously.
I'll give you a couple red, I'll give you a six pack of red bulls.
I'll give you a six pack of red bulls and a, a tenth of meth.
There it was. I like to be there.
Look, look, look, I'm going to be real nasty about this, but I'm going to say it.
Hey, it's like, remember how you set your experience was one pump.
Okay, so realistically
LD would meet me maybe
There are times where I'm having snacks and I'm like, I'd rather go to sleep. It's just it's just fucking too much work
Can we just lay on our side on the side of the bed?
Freaky shit when I was younger, man.
It sucks to be able to do it.
Well, that's the thing, you do it when you're young,
but I would not trade any experiences I've had.
Exactly.
No matter how embarrassing for anything in the world.
I had so much fun.
Then you've got those regrets in your life later on,
like, oh, well, what if I had a threesome?
What if I flopped?
What if I had an orgy?
What if I did this?
Like, you know, it's like, I did all that shit.
Like, well, I haven't done any of that.
Can I do that with you, LD?
No
You're a cop walking well, I'll find something. Yeah. Exactly. Yes, you're laughing. She's not she's not
I care about you I care about
I care about his sister I care about his mom I care about
Yeah, no, there's nothing dude, it's like it's like I hung out with Andy dick. There's nothing you. Oh my god. What do you do you?
Yeah, I told I told Andy dick when I
He said Jordan is apartment. I go
Touch me in a way. I don't like I'm gonna touch you in a way. You definitely don't like, you know, like don't grow
Yeah, like you just fucking grab my cock we're gonna be fucking bro like
I would be in a cock fight and I wouldn't that's what it is.
I don't care. I don't care.
Everybody I'm going to go get
another beer and take a piss.
I'll be right back.
What are you? Are you down?
Mike show up. Mike show up.
You're your last name.
Tell us a story.
Tell us. Tell us about what
happened the last time you were
Ooh, Bear Mountain sounds gay.
What?
I'm sorry.
Mike, oh, oh, shit, look at this.
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, Mike, go to your dick.
Go to your dick, go to your dick.
But show me your abs again.
They're like, they're good.
Damn, I know you had a good body like this. Those are your butt
It's like you're ruining the string this is
I'm gonna save it. I'll save it. You're awesome. Awesome string
Really like you're a fucking asshole. I'm gonna restart